<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quarry Mining_crusher Cone on Universal</title>
    <link>/categorylinks/quarry-mining_crusher-cone/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Quarry Mining_crusher Cone on Universal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categorylinks/quarry-mining_crusher-cone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>E03201</title>
      <link>/stock/E03201/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03201/</guid>
      <description>Rebuilt 2014 Terex BL (Brown Lenox) Kue Ken CT1300 (Medium Coarse) modular mounted cone crusher. Cone size 1300mm (51&amp;rdquo;) , up to 300TPH production. Can take up to 8&amp;rdquo; (200mm) stone. The cone went through a frame up rebuild, new 160kw electric motor fitted, mounted on new floating frame and sub frame, new manufactured 2 way discharge belt fitted under the cone, new galvanized safety walkways and handrails fitted. Electric starter panel can be supplied at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03672</title>
      <link>/stock/E03672/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03672/</guid>
      <description>New / Rebuilt Svedala Allis H36 wheeled mobile cone crushing plant. Output up to 220 t/ph capacity depending of infeed and outfeed size, c/w completely rebuilt Svedala Allis H36 cone unit. new surge hopper and vibrating feeder, new feed conveyor, new discharge conveyor, new electric motors, drives and control panel, new magnet fitted over feed conveyor, new over cone level sensor connected to an inverter to insure constant feed to the cone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03692</title>
      <link>/stock/E03692/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03692/</guid>
      <description>Refurbished 2018 Metso/Nordberg 1560 (HP500) wheeled mobile cone crushing plant. Cone is set up in secondary configuration, max. feed size 175mm (7&amp;rdquo;), producing up to 800 TPH, c/w 2 deck Cedarapids 6202 pre- screen. Delta Manufacturing tri axle carrier, control panel and switch gear, rear fines discharge conveyor, side folding product conveyor, unit factory test run and ready to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03808</title>
      <link>/stock/E03808/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03808/</guid>
      <description>Unused Terex Pegson 1000 modular secondary cone crusher (long throw), c/w base frame, galvanized safety handrails &amp;amp; walkways, 160kW electric motor, lube pack, control unit, over cone hopper, magic eye. All automatic controls located in centralized control cabinet. From 120 -180 TPH capacity depending on feed material and settings. Two way under cone discharge conveyor available at extra cost. Crusher is immediately available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04007</title>
      <link>/stock/E04007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04007/</guid>
      <description>Pegson 1300 Cone Crusher, Remanufactured 2015, skid mounted, output up to 350t/h capacity depending on infeed and outfeed size, c/w 132kW electric motor, new main frame liners fitted, new shroud covers fitted, new mantle fitted, new distribution plate fitted. Crusher is immediately available from stock. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>