<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earthmoving Equipment_loaders Wheeled on Universal</title>
    <link>/categorylinks/earthmoving-equipment_loaders-wheeled/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earthmoving Equipment_loaders Wheeled on Universal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categorylinks/earthmoving-equipment_loaders-wheeled/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>E03169</title>
      <link>/stock/E03169/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03169/</guid>
      <description>Ex army Caterpillar 988B 4x4 forklift, Cabin with ROPS &amp;amp; heater, Caterpillar 3408T diesel powered engine 393 HP. Direct injection 65 degree V8 turbo diesel engine. Variable timing fuel system. Power shift transmission. 24 volt direct electric starting system. Full hydraulic steering system with center point frame articulation. Operating weight w/o tophandler 52 ton. 25 ton lifting capacity. Can Stack 20 to 40 Ft containers two high. Top handler attachment. Tire size 35/65R33.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04333</title>
      <link>/stock/E04333/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04333/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 930 Ex-Army wheel loader, Cab, 4 cylinder Cat 3304 engine with 100HP (75kW), powershift transmission, 20.5R25 Michelin tyres 75% remaining, GP bucket with teeth, engine enclosures, rear counter weight, drawbar, 9.620 Kgs. operating weight. Machine has new paint, very low hours and is in very good technical and optical condition. This is one of the nicest 930&amp;rsquo;s which is available on the market!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04533</title>
      <link>/stock/E04533/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04533/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 990H Wheel Loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, manufactured in 2005, first sold in 2012, V12 Turbocharged Aftercooled Cat C27 ACERT Technology engine with 687HP (512kW), EPA compliant, 3 speed powershift transmission, joystick steering, Rock bucket with teeth, rated payload 16.500 Kgs, operating weight 78.000 Kgs, central grease system, 45/65R38 Michelin tyres on average 85% remaining, work lights. Machine comes straight out of work and is in very clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04811</title>
      <link>/stock/E04811/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04811/</guid>
      <description>Komatsu WA200-6 Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 4 cylinder turbocharged Komatsu SAA4D107E-1 engine with 128HP (95kW), EPA Certified, 4 speed hydrostatic transmission, hydraulic quick release with bucket and forks, 20.5R25 tyres 80% remaining, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, engine enclosures. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04921</title>
      <link>/stock/E04921/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04921/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 980H Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C15 ACERT Technology engine with 348HP (260kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, V-rock bucket with teeth, ride control, Command Control Steering, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, 29.5R25 tyres, 31.330 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04924</title>
      <link>/stock/E04924/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04924/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 980H Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C15 ACERT Technology engine with 348HP (260kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, V-rock bucket with teeth, ride control, Command Control Steering, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, 29.5R25 tyres, 31.330 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04925</title>
      <link>/stock/E04925/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04925/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 950GC Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 225HP (168kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, Full steer, GP bucket with teeth, bucket capacity 3.30 M3, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, 23.5R25 tyres, 18.100 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04926</title>
      <link>/stock/E04926/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04926/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 950GC Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 225HP (168kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, Full steer, GP bucket with teeth, bucket capacity 3.30 M3, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, 23.5R25 tyres, 18.100 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>