<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wheel Loaders on </title>
    <link>/category/wheel-loaders/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wheel Loaders on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/category/wheel-loaders/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>E00360</title>
      <link>/stock/E00360/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E00360/</guid>
      <description>Komatsu WA600-1L Wheel loader, E-ROPS cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder Komatsu SD170 engine with 415 HP, 40.400Kg operating weight, 5.4M3 bucket, 4 step powershift transmission, 35&amp;frasl;65-33 tyres. Machine is in &amp;ldquo;as is&amp;rdquo; running condition and will be sold for spares or repairs. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02963</title>
      <link>/stock/E02963/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02963/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 938G, E-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3126 engine with 161HP (120kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, bucket capacity 2.50 M3, 20.5-25 tyres on average 40% remaining, front and rear work lights. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome. GP bucket with cutting edge available at extra costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04533</title>
      <link>/stock/E04533/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04533/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 990H Wheel Loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, manufactured in 2005, first sold in 2012, V12 Turbocharged Aftercooled Cat C27 ACERT Technology engine with 687HP (512kW), EPA compliant, 3 speed powershift transmission, joystick steering, Rock bucket with teeth, rated payload 16.500 Kgs, operating weight 78.000 Kgs, central grease system, 45/65R38 Michelin tyres on average 85% remaining, work lights. Machine comes straight out of work and is in very clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04800</title>
      <link>/stock/E04800/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04800/</guid>
      <description>Komatsu WA350-3T, O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Komatsu SA6D108E-2 engine, 4 speed powershift transmission, bucket with teeth, work lights, engine enclosures, 20.5-25 tyres, lift cylinders are resealed. Repair pictures available on request. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04812</title>
      <link>/stock/E04812/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04812/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 980G Series II, Delivered new in 2006, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat 3406E engine with 300HP (220kW), 4 speed automatic transmission, refurbished GP Cat bucket with new wear parts, Command Control Steering system, ride control, 29.5R25 tyres, front and rear work lights, 30.500 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04921</title>
      <link>/stock/E04921/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04921/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 980H Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C15 ACERT Technology engine with 348HP (260kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, V-rock bucket with teeth, ride control, Command Control Steering, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, 29.5R25 tyres, 31.330 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04926</title>
      <link>/stock/E04926/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04926/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 950GC Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 225HP (168kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, Full steer, GP bucket with teeth, bucket capacity 3.30 M3, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, 23.5R25 tyres, 18.100 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>