<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>E00127</title>
      <link>/stock/E00127/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E00127/</guid>
      <description>Ford F450, Service truck, V8 Powers stroke diesel engine, 5 speed manual transmission, LHD, standard cab, work bed, welder/generator including cables, fuel tank including pump, 2 air hose reels, bolt on crane, storage boxes, 235/85R16 Michelin tyres 70% remaining. Truck is in good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E00266</title>
      <link>/stock/E00266/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E00266/</guid>
      <description>Doosan 130LCV, Cab with airconditioning, mono boom, 3.05 Mtr. stick, hammer lines, quick coupler, undercarriage on average 75% remaining, 700mm triple grouser pads, GP digging bucket, work lights, 14.000 Kgs operating weight. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E00293</title>
      <link>/stock/E00293/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E00293/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 769D, 40 ton rigid off-road dump truck with cab fire damage, 3408E Cat engine which is not damaged, bodylinders, retarder, 18.00-33 tyres which are 70% on average. Dump truck is easy to repair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E00360</title>
      <link>/stock/E00360/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E00360/</guid>
      <description>Komatsu WA600-1L Wheel loader, E-ROPS cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder Komatsu SD170 engine with 415 HP, 40.400Kg operating weight, 5.4M3 bucket, 4 step powershift transmission, 35&amp;frasl;65-33 tyres. Machine is in &amp;ldquo;as is&amp;rdquo; running condition and will be sold for spares or repairs. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E00477</title>
      <link>/stock/E00477/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E00477/</guid>
      <description>Fully refurbished, self contained mobile impact crusher, crusher opening 600x350mm, maximum feed size 200mm, production 100 TPH, 633 hopper, 3 hammers, 90kw electric engine and starter panel, 235/75R17.5 tyres, new paint. Crusher is in good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E00952</title>
      <link>/stock/E00952/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E00952/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D4H dozer, parts machine. Final drives &amp;amp; transmission available. Please contact us for parts / component price &amp;amp; availability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E00953</title>
      <link>/stock/E00953/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E00953/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7H LGP dozer available for parts. Please contact us for parts / component price &amp;amp; availability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E01555</title>
      <link>/stock/E01555/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E01555/</guid>
      <description>Unused Eurotec hammer, rated for excavators from 4 till 9 ton, fitted with chisel tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E01556</title>
      <link>/stock/E01556/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E01556/</guid>
      <description>Unused Eurotec hammer, rated for excavators from 4 till 9 ton, fitted with chisel tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E01657</title>
      <link>/stock/E01657/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E01657/</guid>
      <description>Nooteboom OSD47VVS 3 axle low bed trailer, 60 ton gross weight, steel suspension, 8.50mtr low bed length, 1.80mtr extendable, 2.5mtr width, winch, 8.25R15 Bridgestone tyres with approx. 75% remaining.2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E01709</title>
      <link>/stock/E01709/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E01709/</guid>
      <description>2 axle step frame trailer, 31510 kgs gross weight, 12.05 mtr length, 8.80 mtr low bed length, wooden floor, 265&amp;frasl;70-19.5 tyres with approx. 80% remaining. Trailer is in very good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02073</title>
      <link>/stock/E02073/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02073/</guid>
      <description>Remanufactured 2012 Terex BL Kue-Ken 915mm X 610mm (36&amp;rdquo; x 24&amp;rdquo;) wheeled jaw crushing plant. Crusher unit fully reconditioned! Capacity up to 180 tph depending on infeed size and product. Electric Drive &amp;amp; switch gear, heavy duty dump hopper, vibrating grizzly section, electric hydraulic power pack, complete new discharge conveyor, complete with new safety rails, ladder and walkways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02138</title>
      <link>/stock/E02138/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02138/</guid>
      <description>Terex-Halco 43-22 crawler drill, Cummins 8.3ltr engine, Onboard compressor, 4mtr drill rods, 6 rods carousel, all pins and bushings on mast are replaced, hoses from drill head to dust collector are replaced, many oil hoses are replaced, all repair pictures are available on request, undercarriage has approx. 90% remaining, 400mm pads. Machine has been workshop tested, repaired, has new paint and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02142</title>
      <link>/stock/E02142/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02142/</guid>
      <description>Unused Portable wheeled screening plant, Metso SH 6x20 3 deck screen, heavy duty Delta manufacturing tandem axle chassis, 1.2 mtr under screen conveyor, full galvinised catwalks on 3 sides, rail mounted chute configuration, 30KW electric drive, chassis mounted control panel with extra switchgear and starters for auxiliary conveyors, up to 800 t/ph capacity. Auxillary stockpilling conveyors from 10 - 18 Mtr. long available at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02154</title>
      <link>/stock/E02154/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02154/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar TH360B tractor equipped with welding package, generator, welding machines, oxygen platform, rear view camera and other options available on request. 4 cyl. Caterpillar 3054E engine,100hp, E-rops cab,4x4x4 conf., 4 speed power-shuttle transmission 32km/h max speed, 16.9-24 tyres, joy stick &amp;amp; remote controlled hydr. Hiab 071AW 7.2 tm crane, 7.2 mtr max reach, hydr.powered 10bar 1080l/min aircompressor 240ltr air receiver. Other crane and compressor options available on request, 2 hydr. operated front stabilizers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02296</title>
      <link>/stock/E02296/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02296/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 345CL, Excavator pipelayer,10 units available, tipping point 88 ton, 9.2mtr. A-frame boom, cab with heater and airco. Braden planetary dual brake lifting and deriking winch, 2 speed Rexroth hydr. piston motors, 19mm rope diameter, hydr. boom stop, anti-two block system, hydraulic joystick control, 3 side working range, can be transported in one load. Machine is in as new condition. For sales and rental info please contact: Tel. +31653853392 or E-mail: John@deltamachinery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02311</title>
      <link>/stock/E02311/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02311/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 345CL, Excavator pipelayer,10 units available, tipping point 88 ton, 9.2mtr. A-frame boom, cab with heater and airco. Braden planetary dual brake lifting and deriking winch, 2 speed Rexroth hydr. piston motors, 19mm rope diameter, hydr. boom stop, anti-two block system, hydraulic joystick control, 3 side working range, can be transported in one load. Machine is in as new condition. For sales and rental info please contact: Tel. +31653853392 or E-mail: John@deltamachinery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02368</title>
      <link>/stock/E02368/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02368/</guid>
      <description>Mobile Kue-Ken 114 jaw crusher, up to 250tph, 42x26 (1100x650) vibrating grizzly feeder, folding discharge conveyor. Caterpillar 3306DI engine, overband magnet, triaxle carrier, 4x hydraulic legs, plant came direct from work and in as is condition. Workshop inspection, repairs, repainting available at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02457</title>
      <link>/stock/E02457/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02457/</guid>
      <description>Joy (Gardner Denver) WB12 6.5&amp;rdquo;x5.0&amp;rdquo; Single-Stage skid mounted air booster, can boost air up to 2300 CFM (65.13 m3/min). It can go to 50 bar. c/w Cat 3406 engine. Engine and compressor are in good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02562</title>
      <link>/stock/E02562/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02562/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D5B, E-rops Cab, Cat 3306DI engine with 105HP (78kW), semi U-blade with tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, drawbar, cutting edge 70% remaining, undercarriage on average 80% remaining, new carrier rollers, new sprockets, 560mm pads, 11.500 Kgs operating weight. Machine has new paint, is workshop tested and is in very good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02595</title>
      <link>/stock/E02595/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02595/</guid>
      <description>2014 new build tray body fitted with twist locks fitted on 2008 used chassis, 88,150 kms, Palfinger 32080 crane fitted with 4 extensions c.w. radio remote control, front and rear telescopic jack legs, upright exhaust, 16 speed manual gearbox, new Pirelli 295/80R22.5 tyres fitted, Mounted on 2008 8x4 Hino 700 series (Very Low Kilometers), 420HP, airco, autolube, right hand drive. Truck is workshop tested and repaired. Truck is in very good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02596</title>
      <link>/stock/E02596/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02596/</guid>
      <description>2014 New manufactured cheese wedge bevertail machinery body, jack legs, fitted on 2008 Hino FYPUKA 700 3241 8x4 truck (Ex Goverment), 118,511 kms, upright exhaust, airco, sunvisor, new Pirelli 295/80R22.5 tyres fitted. 16 spd ZF Gearbox, flashing beacons, c.w. New manufactured cheese wedge bevertail machinery body, jack legs, 35,000 Kgs Design Gross Vehicle Weight, Tare Weight 12,800 Kgs, Design Payload 22,200 Kgs (Depending on local regulations), right hand drive. Truck is workshop inspected and repaired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02604</title>
      <link>/stock/E02604/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02604/</guid>
      <description>Speedstar SS2500/SS40 water drilling rig, mounted on heavy duty oilfield tandem axle trailer with Leveling Jacks, Triple Drum Draw Works, Twin (2) Detroit diesel 471 Deck engines with manual transmission, 18 inch rotary table, 18m hydraulically raised mast, (Mast replaced in 2010), with hook block, swivel, operators control station and console, new 11.00-20 tyres. This drilling rig has new paint, is repaired and is in clean condition. Truck is not included.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02640</title>
      <link>/stock/E02640/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02640/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 953 tractor equipped with welding package, generator, welding machines, oxygen platform, rear view camera and other options available on request. 6 cyl. Caterpillar 3116T engine, 120hp, E-rops cab, 10.5km/h max. speed, joy stick &amp;amp; remote controlled hydr. Hiab 071AW 7.2 tm crane, 7.2 mtr max reach, hydr. powered 10 bar 1080l/min aircompressor 240ltr air receiver. Other crane and compressor options available on request. We have many welding tractors in our rental fleet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02750</title>
      <link>/stock/E02750/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02750/</guid>
      <description>Pipe carrier kit fitted on Caterpillar D8T Dozer. Pipe saddles can be changed to transport various pipe diameters from 36 to 60 inches. Kit can be easily removed and re-installed on Cat D8T/R tractor. E-rops cab with air-conditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C15 ACERT Technology engine with 359HP (268kW), 3 speed power-shift transmission, joystick controls, New Caterpillar undercarriage fitted, 600mm pads, 35.000Kgs operating weight, front &amp;amp; rear work lights. 4 Kits available from stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02937</title>
      <link>/stock/E02937/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02937/</guid>
      <description>2001 Hausherr Viper H Series crawler drill rig, c/w enclosed operator cabin, suitable for Down The Hole drilling up to 150mm diamater hole, 81kw Caterpillar/Perkins engine, 4.6m drill mast lenght, 40kn pull down force, 40kn withdrawal force, can take 76-95mm rods, 8 rod carousel, rig has gone through the workshop with many components repaired/replaced where applicable. All repair pictures are available upon request. We have a range of mobile diesel air compressors available to suit if necessary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02943</title>
      <link>/stock/E02943/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02943/</guid>
      <description>Komatsu GD530A-1, Low profile E-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Komatsu diesel engine, powershift transmission, 12ft (3.65 Mtr) moldboard, new cutting edge, centershift, hydr. tipcontrol, scarifier, rear ripper with full set of new shanks, engine enclosures, 14.00-24 tyres 70%. Machine has new paint and is in very clean condition. Inspections are welcome. All manuals are available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02963</title>
      <link>/stock/E02963/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02963/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 938G, E-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3126 engine with 161HP (120kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, bucket capacity 2.50 M3, 20.5-25 tyres on average 40% remaining, front and rear work lights. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome. GP bucket with cutting edge available at extra costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03000</title>
      <link>/stock/E03000/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03000/</guid>
      <description>New manufactured in 2013 Metso SH 6x20 (3 deck) mobile screening plant c/w 3 units brand new XROK Transporter 4030E stockpilling conveyors. Screen size 20ftx6ft (6.00x1.80mtr). Length stockpile conveyor 40ft (12.00 mtr), belt width 30inch (750mm). Capacity up to 800 t/ph. Heavy duty Delta manufacturing tandem axle chassis, 1.2 mtr under screen conveyor, full galvinised catwalks on 3 sides, rail mounted chute configuration. Chassis mounted control panel with extra switchgear and starters for conveyors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03126</title>
      <link>/stock/E03126/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03126/</guid>
      <description>Macgen 450 KVA Diesel Generator, 8 cylinder turbocharged Scania DC14 engine, 1500RPM, engine is mounted on robust rubber anti-vibration mounts on an open skid frame, Marrelli Altenator, 240&amp;frasl;415 volts, 50 Hz, 4 pole circuit breaker. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03169</title>
      <link>/stock/E03169/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03169/</guid>
      <description>Ex army Caterpillar 988B 4x4 forklift, Cabin with ROPS &amp;amp; heater, Caterpillar 3408T diesel powered engine 393 HP. Direct injection 65 degree V8 turbo diesel engine. Variable timing fuel system. Power shift transmission. 24 volt direct electric starting system. Full hydraulic steering system with center point frame articulation. Operating weight w/o tophandler 52 ton. 25 ton lifting capacity. Can Stack 20 to 40 Ft containers two high. Top handler attachment. Tire size 35/65R33.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03201</title>
      <link>/stock/E03201/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03201/</guid>
      <description>Rebuilt 2014 Terex BL (Brown Lenox) Kue Ken CT1300 (Medium Coarse) modular mounted cone crusher. Cone size 1300mm (51&amp;rdquo;) , up to 300TPH production. Can take up to 8&amp;rdquo; (200mm) stone. The cone went through a frame up rebuild, new 160kw electric motor fitted, mounted on new floating frame and sub frame, new manufactured 2 way discharge belt fitted under the cone, new galvanized safety walkways and handrails fitted. Electric starter panel can be supplied at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03222</title>
      <link>/stock/E03222/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03222/</guid>
      <description>EPE PL95H, Hydrostatic pipelayers,10 units available, CE marked, 95 ton lifting capacity, Caterpillar C13 Tier IIIA engine 440HP, Linde hydrostatic transmission,10 km/h max speed, 9.0mtr. A frame boom, 2 Braden planetary dual brake winches, 2 speed Rexroth hydr. motors, 19mm rope, hydr. joystick control.
For more info please contact John at Delta Pipeline Machinery: E-mail: John@deltamachinery.nl Phone: +31 888 966 966</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03299</title>
      <link>/stock/E03299/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03299/</guid>
      <description>Baxter 900x300mm (36&amp;rdquo;x12&amp;rdquo;) Single Toggle Granulator Jaw Crusher, Remanufactured 2013, modular mounted, suitable for secondary crushing after primary jaw crusher, up to 100 TPH capacity depending on infeed and outfeed size, c/w modular base frame, under crusher cross discharge conveyor, electric motor, output size 90-40mm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03335</title>
      <link>/stock/E03335/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03335/</guid>
      <description>Hino 700FY with crane, 2007 8x4 Hino 700 series, 420HP, 221,464 kms, body with twist locks, HIAB 220C-5 crane fitted with 5 extensions c.w. radio remote control and rear legs, airco, upright exhaust, 16 speed manual gearbox, NEW Pirelli 295/80R22.5 tyres fitted, reverse camera, aluminium tool lockers, right hand drive. Truck is workshop tested and repaired. Truck is in very good and clean condition. Inspections are welcome!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03352</title>
      <link>/stock/E03352/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03352/</guid>
      <description>Frick eclipse steam engine tractor, tractor is in original condition. Nice restoration object!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03353</title>
      <link>/stock/E03353/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03353/</guid>
      <description>Aultmann &amp;amp; Taylor steam engine tractor, tractor is in original condition, nice restoration object!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03447</title>
      <link>/stock/E03447/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03447/</guid>
      <description>Hyster H3.5FT forklift, E-rops cab with heater, 4 cylinder Yanmar 4TNE98-NMH engine with 66HP (48,5kW), max. lifting capacity 3.500Kgs, Duramatch transmission, duplex mast length 4.30Mtr, fork length 1.14Mtr, side shift, front and rear work lights, beacon, 250-15 front tyres and 6.50-10 rear tyres 85% remaining, CE marked. Forklift is in very good condition. LH cab door is available (not shown on pictures).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03453</title>
      <link>/stock/E03453/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03453/</guid>
      <description>Refurbished Kue-Ken 106, 1100x305mm (42x12&amp;rdquo;) skid mounted modular jaw crusher. New diaphragm, new cheek plates, new keeper plate, new flow switch, new skid mount, new motor stand, new oils and filters. Crusher is in good condition and immediately available. Crusher can be used in a secondary or tertiary application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03482</title>
      <link>/stock/E03482/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03482/</guid>
      <description>New and Unused Caterpillar 330D LN, Cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 268HP (200kW), mono boom, 2.15 Mtr stick, hammer lines, check valves, Cat bucket with teeth, 600mm triple grouser shoes, full set of track guides, work lights, 37.000 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine is immediately available! Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03484</title>
      <link>/stock/E03484/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03484/</guid>
      <description>Montracon 3 axle semi curtain side trailer, ABS, back doors, sliding side, 13.7 Mtr length, 2.55 Mtr width, air suspension, 385/65R22.5 tyres, gross weight 39.000 Kgs. Trailer is in very good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03672</title>
      <link>/stock/E03672/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03672/</guid>
      <description>New / Rebuilt Svedala Allis H36 wheeled mobile cone crushing plant. Output up to 220 t/ph capacity depending of infeed and outfeed size, c/w completely rebuilt Svedala Allis H36 cone unit. new surge hopper and vibrating feeder, new feed conveyor, new discharge conveyor, new electric motors, drives and control panel, new magnet fitted over feed conveyor, new over cone level sensor connected to an inverter to insure constant feed to the cone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03692</title>
      <link>/stock/E03692/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03692/</guid>
      <description>Refurbished 2018 Metso/Nordberg 1560 (HP500) wheeled mobile cone crushing plant. Cone is set up in secondary configuration, max. feed size 175mm (7&amp;rdquo;), producing up to 800 TPH, c/w 2 deck Cedarapids 6202 pre- screen. Delta Manufacturing tri axle carrier, control panel and switch gear, rear fines discharge conveyor, side folding product conveyor, unit factory test run and ready to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03698</title>
      <link>/stock/E03698/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03698/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7G, E-rops cab, Cat 3306 engine, 3 speed powershift transmission, semi U blade/tilt, 610mm pads, undercarriage 75% remaining, drawbar. Machine comes straight out of work and is in ex job site condition. Rear ripper or rear pulling winch available at extra cost. Machine can be painted at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03718</title>
      <link>/stock/E03718/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03718/</guid>
      <description>New manufactured Delta 40 ton mobile surge bin, c/w single axle 5th wheeled coupling, Skako vibrating tray feeder, electric control panel enclosed in dust proof cabined, 385/65R22 tyres, umbilical level sensor for over crusher wired into control cabined for start/stop function of feeder. Can feed up to 250 TPH.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03808</title>
      <link>/stock/E03808/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03808/</guid>
      <description>Unused Terex Pegson 1000 modular secondary cone crusher (long throw), c/w base frame, galvanized safety handrails &amp;amp; walkways, 160kW electric motor, lube pack, control unit, over cone hopper, magic eye. All automatic controls located in centralized control cabinet. From 120 -180 TPH capacity depending on feed material and settings. Two way under cone discharge conveyor available at extra cost. Crusher is immediately available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03829</title>
      <link>/stock/E03829/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03829/</guid>
      <description>New &amp;amp; Unused Ingersoll Rand ECM350 towed wagon drill, c/w IR DTH rotary head, can drill 85 mm to 127mm holes and capacity up to 150m deep, set up for down the hole (DTH) rotation drilling, 3,900 Nm Torque @ 8 bar 10,000LB pullback, takes 3m rods, rig weight 5,443 Kg, 300mm Track Shoes, manifold for water injection, safety check valves on main cylinders.** Drill rods, hammers, tooling etc. can be supplied to customers specification at extra cost on request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03940</title>
      <link>/stock/E03940/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03940/</guid>
      <description>Atlas Copco XA350 Ex-Army towable aircompressor, 8 cylinder Deutz F8L413F aircooled engine, advised working pressure 8 Bar, 740CFM (21.0 M3/min) free air delivery, Michelin 7.50R16 XCL tyres 85% remaining. Compressor comes straight out of work, has low hours and is in clean condition. Compressor can be painted in company colours or original Atlas Copco colours at extra cost. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03976</title>
      <link>/stock/E03976/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03976/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Terex-Cedarapids TSH6163-32 screenbox, 3 deck screen box, mounted on floating sub frame, 16ftx5ft, c/w 30kW electric motor and guards. Screenbox is ready for immediate dispatch! Wide range of quarry equipment / mobile conveyors to suit available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03979</title>
      <link>/stock/E03979/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03979/</guid>
      <description>Parker 105 Kubitizer Primary/Secondary impact crusher, c/w 150KW electric motor, output capacity 175-200 Ton/Hour, feed size 7&amp;rdquo;-12&amp;rdquo; (175-350 mm), operating weight 14.000 Kgs. New set of impact hammers in stock which can be supplied at extra cost. Crusher can be painted on request at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03990</title>
      <link>/stock/E03990/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03990/</guid>
      <description>Nooteboom MCO-97-06 Semi step frame trailer, 6 axles, hydraulic suspension, 12 Ton axles, 4 axles hydraulic steering, trailer width 2.72 Mtr, goose neck length 4.35 Mtr, loading deck length 11.95 Mtr, total length 16.30 Mtr, 285/70R19.5 tyres. Trailer is immediately available from stock, trailer needs some repairs. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03991</title>
      <link>/stock/E03991/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03991/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar SS-250B soil stabiliser, enclosed cab, ROPS, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat 3406 engine, 3 speed hydrostatic transmission, speed meters miles and KM, 2WD, front and rear steering, tyres front 28L-26, tyres rear 14.9R24, rotor width 240Cm, rotor diameter 120Cm, tips on average 90% remaining (some replaced), PTO driven rotor. Machine comes straight out of work, has new paint and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04007</title>
      <link>/stock/E04007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04007/</guid>
      <description>Pegson 1300 Cone Crusher, Remanufactured 2015, skid mounted, output up to 350t/h capacity depending on infeed and outfeed size, c/w 132kW electric motor, new main frame liners fitted, new shroud covers fitted, new mantle fitted, new distribution plate fitted. Crusher is immediately available from stock. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04027</title>
      <link>/stock/E04027/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04027/</guid>
      <description>Deutz D4006A, Deutz F3L912 3 cylinder engine, 40 HP, 4-WD Sige 3500 axle, 3 point linkage, 540&amp;frasl;1000 PTO. Tractor is in good and clean condition, tyres 13.6-28 (70%) and 7.50-18 (30%). Wir sprechen Deutsch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04063</title>
      <link>/stock/E04063/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04063/</guid>
      <description>Deutz D6005, 4 cyl. deutz F4L812 engine, 3 point linkage, PTO, toplink, hydr.spoolvalves. 16.9-30 rear tyres.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04070</title>
      <link>/stock/E04070/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04070/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar TH62, enclosed cab with FOPS, Rebuild Caterpillar 3054 engine with 100HP (75kW), 4 speed powershift transmission, 4x4x4 configuration, 4WD, dual axis joystick control, brand new seat, rated load capacity 3.000 Kgs, max. lift height 7.6 Mtr, 7.700 Kgs operating weight, quick coupler, extra hydr. spoolvalve, brand new 17.5LR24 tyres. Machine has new paint, is workshop tested, fully repaired and is in very good and clean condition. Machine is including pallet fork &amp;amp; GP bucket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04233</title>
      <link>/stock/E04233/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04233/</guid>
      <description>Dynapac CA15D, Single smooth drum vibrating roller, canopy, 4 cylinder Ford engine with 68HP (51 kW), 7.000 Kgs. operating weight, drum width 1.68 Mtr. (66 inch), drum diameter 1.22 Mtr. (48 inch), 13.6-28 tyres 90% remaining, new seat. Machine has new paint, is workshop tested, fully repaired and is in very good and clean condition. Machine has very low hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04269</title>
      <link>/stock/E04269/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04269/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D4E fitted with Midwestern hydraulic pipelayer kit, Caterpillar 3304 engine with 75HP (56kW), ROPS, hydraulic boom and hook winches, rubber boom protection, operating weight approx. 11.000 Kgs, wire ropes in good condition, undercarriage on average 75% remaining. Machine comes straight from job-site and is in very good and clean condition. Machine for sale or rent, subject to terms and conditions. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04291</title>
      <link>/stock/E04291/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04291/</guid>
      <description>Case Vibromax 1102D vibratory roller, Cab, Drum Drive, Deutz engine, 2.16 Mtr. drum width, Brand new 23.1-26 tyres, hydrostatic transmission, new seat. Machine has new paint, low hours, is workshop tested, has new paint and is in very good and clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04292</title>
      <link>/stock/E04292/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04292/</guid>
      <description>John Deere 1630 High Crop Tractor, canopy, powersteering, 3 cylinder JD engine, 3 point linkage, PTO, toplink, hydr.spoolvalves, 7.50-16 front tyres and 11.2R44 (270/95R44) rear tyres 80% remaining. Tractor is in very good technical and clean condition. Very clean original tractor!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04333</title>
      <link>/stock/E04333/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04333/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 930 Ex-Army wheel loader, Cab, 4 cylinder Cat 3304 engine with 100HP (75kW), powershift transmission, 20.5R25 Michelin tyres 75% remaining, GP bucket with teeth, engine enclosures, rear counter weight, drawbar, 9.620 Kgs. operating weight. Machine has new paint, very low hours and is in very good technical and optical condition. This is one of the nicest 930&amp;rsquo;s which is available on the market!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04336</title>
      <link>/stock/E04336/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04336/</guid>
      <description>Kue-Ken 95 jaw crusher, 915mm X 610mm (36&amp;rdquo; x 24&amp;rdquo;) jaw opening. Up to 180 TPH crushing capacity. Internal mechanism repaired/replaced, Crusher has new paint, is fully workshop inspected and repaired. Wide range of crusher/screening equipment available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04344</title>
      <link>/stock/E04344/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04344/</guid>
      <description>Bomag BW212 vibrating single drum roller, Cab, 6 cylinder Deutz F6L912 engine with 112HP (82kW), drum width 2.10 Mtr, 23.1-26 tyres, hydrostatic transmission, 11.200 Kgs operating weight. Machine has new paint, is workshop inspected and is in very good and clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04374</title>
      <link>/stock/E04374/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04374/</guid>
      <description>MAN TGS32.360 with TEKA concrete pump 42 Mtr, 476,740 km, cab with airconditioning, 8x4 configuration, manual gearbox, 295/80R22.5 tyres.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04389</title>
      <link>/stock/E04389/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04389/</guid>
      <description>Ford 6710, Cab, powersteering, 4 cylinder engine, 3 point linkage, PTO, drawbar, toplink, hydr.spoolvalves, 7.50-20 front tyres and 16.9-38 rear tyres. Tractor is in working order and clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04398</title>
      <link>/stock/E04398/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04398/</guid>
      <description>Brand New Xrok Granite 400 self propelled pipeline padding machine, High capacity 2 Deck Screen-Box,11.5 M2 screening area, up to 400 t/ph capacity, many different screen options available to process dry, wet &amp;amp; sticky material, available with 225 HP Caterpillar C7.1, Tier IIIB &amp;amp; Tier 4 Final, CE Marked, Inclined hopper allowing maximum visibility for excavator operator, side to side conveyor with hydraulic deflector plate, 2 speed hydrostatic drive, remote control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04403</title>
      <link>/stock/E04403/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04403/</guid>
      <description>Massey Ferguson 575, 2-door cab, 3-gearlevels, 3-point linkage, PTO, hydr. spoolvalves, 7.50-18 front tyres, 13.6-28 rear tyres. Tractor is in ex farm- and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04405</title>
      <link>/stock/E04405/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04405/</guid>
      <description>Ingersoll Rand CM780D Crawler Rock Drill, Cab with airconditioning, Remanufactured 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C12 engine with 425HP (317kW), automatic rod changer, pull back force 45.530 N, 2-stage rotary screw air compressor, dust collector + pres cyclone, central grease system, rear view camera, undercarriage on average 80% remaining, 350mm pads, all pipes and drill head included, operating weight 21.000 Kgs, CE marked. 3.428 engine hours, 9.809 Drill hours. Machine is workshop tested and is in good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04406</title>
      <link>/stock/E04406/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04406/</guid>
      <description>Atlas Copco CM780D Crawler Rock Drill, Cab with airconditioning, Remanufactured 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C13 engine with 445HP (317kW) 0 Hours! Automatic rod changer, pull back force 45.530 N, 2-stage rotary screw air compressor, dust collector + pres cyclone, incl. drill rods, rear view camera, undercarriage on average 75% remaining, 350mm pads, operating weight 22.230 Kgs, CE marked. 6.524 machine hours, 3.424 drill hours. Machine is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04445</title>
      <link>/stock/E04445/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04445/</guid>
      <description>Brand new Doosan/Ingersoll-Rand SHP650 High Capacity Portable Air Compressor, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cummins 6CTA8.3 engine with 260HP (194kW) @ 2200 RPM, max. free air delivery 18.4 M3/min (650CFM), rated pressure 19 Bar (275 psi/ 1.9 MPa), 7.00-16 tyres, operating weight 4.420 Kgs. 2 Units immediately available from stock. Inspections are welcome. Available for sale or rent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04446</title>
      <link>/stock/E04446/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04446/</guid>
      <description>Brand new Doosan/Ingersoll-Rand SHP650 High Capacity Portable Air Compressor, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cummins 6CTA8.3 engine with 260HP (194kW) @ 2200 RPM, max. free air delivery 18.4 M3/min (650CFM), rated pressure 19 Bar (275 psi/ 1.9 MPa), 7.00-16 tyres, operating weight 4.420 Kgs. 2 Units immediately available from stock. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04450</title>
      <link>/stock/E04450/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04450/</guid>
      <description>Ford 8401, Australian import, very rare tractor, only 720 units were built, cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder Ford engine, 110 HP, powersteering, 3-point linkage, PTO, hydr. spoolvalves, Dual Power, full set front weights, 11.00-16 front tyres &amp;amp; 23.1-34 Firestone rear tyres. Tractor runs fine and is in clean condition for age. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04456</title>
      <link>/stock/E04456/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04456/</guid>
      <description>Self propelled Phoenix MKVII chip spreader, 4WD, hydraulic extendable spreader 2.50 - 3.85 Mtr working width, canopy, 6 cylinder Ford Powerstar engine, manual transmission, variable speed drum roller, variable speed feed belts, hydraulic folding rear hoppers, 425/65R22.5 Bridgestone tyres, powersteering. Machine is Ex-Government and comes straight from work. Machine has low hours, new paint and is in clean condition. 2 Similar machines available. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04457</title>
      <link>/stock/E04457/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04457/</guid>
      <description>Self propelled Phoenix MKVII chip spreader, 4WD, hydraulic extendable spreader 2.50 - 3.85 Mtr working width, canopy, 6 cylinder Ford Powerstar engine, manual transmission, variable speed drum roller, variable speed feed belts, hydraulic folding rear hoppers, 425/65R22.5 Bridgestone tyres, powersteering. Machine is Ex-Government and comes straight from work. Machine has low hours, new paint and is in clean condition. 2 Similar machines available. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04458</title>
      <link>/stock/E04458/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04458/</guid>
      <description>Ford 5610 Series II, Cab, powersteering, 4 cylinder engine, 3 point linkage, PTO, drawbar, hydr.spoolvalves, 7.50-18 front tyres and 16.9-34 rear tyres. Tractor is in working order and clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04467</title>
      <link>/stock/E04467/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04467/</guid>
      <description>Available for rent 20 units Caterpillar 594H S/N# 96V sideboom / pipelayers. All units are frame up rebuilds or fully repaired with servo controlled wet deck conversions, equipped with Braden - Paccar winches with 2 speed Bosch Rexroth hydr. motors, Kawasaki hydr. main pumps, Pat Kruger LML safe load system, Certified ROPS &amp;amp; FOPS fitted, all work orders and pictures of repairs &amp;amp; hydr. conversion available upon request. Tractor has D353 engine 410HP, 3 speed power-shift transmission and drawbar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04478</title>
      <link>/stock/E04478/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04478/</guid>
      <description>Manitou MRT1432 Rotary Telescopic Handler, E-rops cab, Perkins 1104T engine with 101HP (74.5kW), EPA Certified, 2 speed hydrostatic transmission, 4WD, 4x4x4 configuration, forks, mechanical quick coupler, extra hydr. spoolvalve, 4 hydraulic stabilizers, max. lift capacity 3.200 Kgs, max. lift height 13.82 Mtr, max. reach 11.63 Mtr, brand new 16.0/70-20 tyres, operating weight 12.340 Kgs, drawbar, CE marked. Machine is driving but electric &amp;amp; hydraulic system need repairs. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04479</title>
      <link>/stock/E04479/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04479/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 422E Backhoe Loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, Cat 3054C Non-electronic turbocharged engine with 94HP (69kW), 4WD, 4 speed transmission, max. speed 40 Km/Hr, hydrostatic steering system, 4-in-1 bucket with teeth and flip-over forks, hydr. extendable stick, operating weight 7.210 Kgs, 12.5&amp;frasl;80-18 front tyres &amp;amp; 16.9-28 rear tyres, front &amp;amp; rear work lights. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04481</title>
      <link>/stock/E04481/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04481/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar CP533E vibrating single drum padfoot roller, 4 cylinder Cat 3054CT turbocharged engine, 130HP (96kW), canopy, 12.000 Kgs operating weight, drum drive, 2 speed hydrostatic drive, 2.13 Mtr drum width, 2 step vibrating, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, 23.1-26 tyres approx. 80% remaining. Machine has low hours and is in clean condition. Inspections welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04488</title>
      <link>/stock/E04488/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04488/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7G Ex-Army dozer, Machine has 462 Hrs from new, O-rops cab with sweeps, engine enclosures, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), semi U blade/tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, undercarriage 95% remaining, 610mm pads, rear pulling winch, new seat, new paint in Caterpillar colour, 22.500 Kgs operating weight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04513</title>
      <link>/stock/E04513/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04513/</guid>
      <description>Fordson E27, 2WD, petrol engine, mechanically refurbished tractor, 3-point linkage, PTO, brand new tyres, rear tyres 13.6-36, front tyres 6.00-19. Electric system needs attention. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04533</title>
      <link>/stock/E04533/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04533/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 990H Wheel Loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, manufactured in 2005, first sold in 2012, V12 Turbocharged Aftercooled Cat C27 ACERT Technology engine with 687HP (512kW), EPA compliant, 3 speed powershift transmission, joystick steering, Rock bucket with teeth, rated payload 16.500 Kgs, operating weight 78.000 Kgs, central grease system, 45/65R38 Michelin tyres on average 85% remaining, work lights. Machine comes straight out of work and is in very clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04537</title>
      <link>/stock/E04537/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04537/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336EL, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C9.3 ATAAC engine with 300HP (224kW), Tier 4 Interim, EPA, mono boom, 3.90 Mtr stick, GP Cat bucket with new teeth, hydr. quick coupler, 75% undercarriage, 850mm triple grouser pads, new sprockets, new top rollers, work lights, rear view camera, operating weight 36.100 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04539</title>
      <link>/stock/E04539/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04539/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336EL, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C9.3 ATAAC engine with 300HP (224kW), Tier 4 Interim, EPA, mono boom, 3.20 Mtr stick, GP bucket with new teeth, bucket width 1.40 Mtr, hammer lines, 80% undercarriage, 850mm triple grouser pads, work lights, rear view camera, operating weight 36.100 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04561</title>
      <link>/stock/E04561/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04561/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D8T Dozer, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C15 ACERT Technology engine with 359HP (268kW), Tier 4 Interim, EPA, 4 barrel SS-ripper with hydr. pin puller, differential steering, wrist control steering, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, rear view camera. Machine comes straight out of work and is in very clean condition. Currently located in Houston Texas, USA. Machine is available for sale or rent, subject to terms and conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04576</title>
      <link>/stock/E04576/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04576/</guid>
      <description>AMS PowerProbe 9635 Geotechnical core drill, drill has only 1014 working hours, PTO powered, 175ft lb hydraulic hammer, high speed auger, high pressure pump, 10&amp;rsquo; x 15&amp;rdquo; drill rod, direct push sampling, side-to-side and in-and-out slide base, hollow stem capabilities, 2-speed 5000 ft lb auger drive head, 80&amp;rdquo; probe stroke for use of up to 5&amp;rsquo; tooling, 2400 psi-12GPM pump, hydraulic oil cooler, 33000 lb push down force, 47500 lb pull back force, adjustable mast for angled probing &amp;amp; drilling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04618</title>
      <link>/stock/E04618/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04618/</guid>
      <description>Ex-army Caterpillar 130G, Sold new in 2007, only 201 Hrs from new! Machine is in as-new condition, Low profile E-rops cab, 12ft (3.65Mtr) moldboard, scarifier, engine enclosures, 13.00-24 tyres. Machine is in very clean condition. Machine can be repainted in original Cat colors at extra cost. Rear ripper can be supplied at extra cost. Inspections are welcome. 15 units available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04625</title>
      <link>/stock/E04625/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04625/</guid>
      <description>Ex-army Caterpillar 130G, Delivered new in 2002, only 545 Hrs from new! Machine is in as-new condition, Low profile O-rops cab, 12ft (3.65Mtr) moldboard, scarifier, engine enclosures, 13.00-24 tyres. Machine is in very clean condition. Machine can be repainted in original Cat colors at extra cost. Rear ripper can be supplied at extra cost. Inspections are welcome. 15 units available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04626</title>
      <link>/stock/E04626/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04626/</guid>
      <description>Ex-army Caterpillar 130G, Sold new in 2007, only 423 hrs from new! Used for Demo / Training only, Caterpillar engine 147HP, machine is in as-new condition, Low profile E-rops cab, 12ft (3.65Mtr) moldboard, new cutting edge, scarifier, new MS rear ripper fitted, engine enclosures, 13.00-24 tyres. Machine is in very clean and good condition. Operating and parts manual available with the machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04645</title>
      <link>/stock/E04645/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04645/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 320DL, Cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C6.4 ACERT Technology engine with 138HP (103kW), mono boom, 2.92 Mtr stick, hammer lines, check valves, GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 1.35 Mtr, undercarriage on average 70% remaining, 700mm triple grouser pads, new sprockets, new carrier rollers, 22.900 Kgs operating weight, work lights, rear view camera, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04649</title>
      <link>/stock/E04649/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04649/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 320C, Cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Non-electronic Cat 3066TAA engine with 138HP (103kW), EPA Certified, mono boom, Smartboom, 2.90 Mtr stick, check valves, hammer lines, hydr. quick coupler, GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 1.25 Mtr, rear view camera, undercarriage on average 75% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04650</title>
      <link>/stock/E04650/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04650/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 320BL Excavator, cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3066 engine with 132HP (99kW), mono boom, 2.90 Mtr stick, hammer lines, check valves, GP bucket with teeth, hydr. quick coupler, undercarriage on average 75% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, work lights, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04652</title>
      <link>/stock/E04652/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04652/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 312BL, cab with airconditioning, 4 cylinder turbocharged 3054 engine with 91HP (68kW), mono boom, hydr. quick coupler, ditch cleaning bucket, undercarriage on average 75% remaining, 700mm triple grouser pads, work lights, 12.800 Kgs operating weight. Machine comes straight out of work and is in very clean condition. Inspections are welcome. Expected October 2018</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04664</title>
      <link>/stock/E04664/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04664/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D6T XL, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C9 ACERT Technology engine with 185HP (138kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, wrist control steering, differential steering, semi-U blade with tilt, new cutting edge, undercarriage average 85% remaining, drawbar, counterweight, front &amp;amp; rear work lights. Ripper or winch can be attached at extra cost. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04677</title>
      <link>/stock/E04677/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04677/</guid>
      <description>John Deere 6410, 4WD, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 4 cylinder turbocharged JD engine with 104HP (78kW), PowerQuad transmission, drawbar, trailer hitch, PTO, electronic 3-point linkage, hydr. spoolvalves, front 3-point hitch, front PTO, air brake system, original JD 651 frontendloader, 520/70R38 Alliance rear tyres &amp;amp; 420/70R28 Vredestein front tyres, front &amp;amp; rear work lights. Tractor comes straight out of work and is in very clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04680</title>
      <link>/stock/E04680/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04680/</guid>
      <description>Hino 700FY tarspreader, RHD, twin burners, Rincheval 2.40 - 4.10 Mtr extendable spray bar, spray &amp;amp; distance meter + printer, 8x4 configuration, manual gearbox, 295/80R22.5 tyres, rear view camera. Truck comes straight out of work. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04690</title>
      <link>/stock/E04690/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04690/</guid>
      <description>Mercedes-Benz 1820 tarspreader, RHD, 2.40 Mtr spray bar, twin burners, hydraulic bitumen pump, 4x2 configuration, manual gearbox, 12R22.5 tyres on average 85% remaining. Truck is Ex Goverment and comes straight out of work. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04692</title>
      <link>/stock/E04692/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04692/</guid>
      <description>Ex-army Caterpillar 130G, Sold new in 2008, only 971 hrs on meter. Machine is in as-new condition, Low profile E-rops cab, 12ft (3.65Mtr) moldboard, scarifier, engine enclosures, 13.00-24 tyres. Machine is in very clean condition. Machine can be repainted in original Cat colors at extra cost. Rear ripper can be supplied at extra cost. Inspections are welcome. 15 units available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04695</title>
      <link>/stock/E04695/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04695/</guid>
      <description>Ex-army Caterpillar 130G, Sold new in 2007, Machine is in as-new condition,183 hrs on meter, Low profile E-rops cab, 12ft (3.65Mtr) moldboard with new cutting edge, scarifier, engine enclosures, 13.00-24 tyres. Machine is in very clean condition. Machine can be repainted in original Cat colors at extra cost. Rear ripper can be supplied at extra cost. Inspections are welcome. 15 units available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04719</title>
      <link>/stock/E04719/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04719/</guid>
      <description>Ex-army Caterpillar 130G, Sold new in 2008, Only 600 Hrs on meter! Machine is in as-new condition, Low profile E-rops cab, 12ft (3.65Mtr) moldboard with new cutting edges, scarifier, engine enclosures, 13.00-24 tyres. Machine is in very clean condition. Machine can be repainted in original Cat colors at extra cost. Rear ripper can be supplied at extra cost. Inspections are welcome. 15 units available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04723</title>
      <link>/stock/E04723/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04723/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 12H motor grader, Low profile E-rops cab, 6 cylinder Caterpillar 3306B Non-electronic engine with 165HP (123kW), 8F-6R powershift transmission, 14ft (4.26 Mtr) moldboard, hydr. tip control, centershift, new cutting edge, 14.200 Kgs operating weight, drawbar, 14.00-24 tyres on average 40% remaining. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome. Rear ripper can be fitted on request at extra costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04736</title>
      <link>/stock/E04736/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04736/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D6G XL Series II, delivered new in 2009, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat 3306DIT Non-electronic engine with 162HP (119kW), 3 speed Non-electronic powershift transmission, Semi U-blade with tilt, new cutting edge, undercarriage on average 75% remaining, engine enclosures, front and rear work lights, drawbar, operating weight 16.880 Kgs. Machine has low hours and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04739</title>
      <link>/stock/E04739/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04739/</guid>
      <description>Unused Laurini PW400HY paywelder, canopy, joystick controlled hydrostatic transmission, Maxilift 040.3L crane class H2-B3, Mecc Alte generator 3 phase 400V, bottle rack, 570mm pads, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, CE marked. 3 Machines immediately available from stock. Available for sale or rent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04740</title>
      <link>/stock/E04740/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04740/</guid>
      <description>Unused Laurini PW400HY paywelder, canopy, joystick controlled hydrostatic transmission, Maxilift 040.3L crane class H2-B3, Mecc Alte generator 3 phase 400V, bottle rack, 570mm pads, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, CE marked. 3 Machines immediately available from stock. Available for sale or rent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04745</title>
      <link>/stock/E04745/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04745/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7F Ex-Army dozer, only 943 hours since new! O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat engine 200HP, Semi U-blade with tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, undercarriage average 90% remaining, 560mm pads, Hyster rear pulling winch. Machine can be supplied including independent Caterpillar TA inspection, can be equipped with a rear ripper and yellow paint at extra costs. Machine is in good and clean condition. 5 Units expected soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04750</title>
      <link>/stock/E04750/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04750/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 824G, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat 3406C engine with 315HP (235kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, blade with double tilt, Command Control Steering, 29.5R29 Bridgestone front tyres &amp;amp; 29.5R29 Michelin rear tyres, 28.495 Kgs operating weight, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, fast fill fuel system, fire suppression system, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04755</title>
      <link>/stock/E04755/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04755/</guid>
      <description>Ex-army Caterpillar 130G, Sold new in 2008, Only 386 Hrs from new! Machine is in as-new condition, Low profile E-rops cab, 12ft (3.65Mtr) moldboard, scarifier, engine enclosures, 13.00-24 tyres. Machine is in very clean condition. New MS rear ripper fitted and new Cat paint. Inspections are welcome. 15 units available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04757</title>
      <link>/stock/E04757/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04757/</guid>
      <description>Ex-army Caterpillar 130G, Sold new in 2007, Only 112 Hrs from new! Machine is in as-new condition, Low profile E-rops cab, 12ft (3.65Mtr) moldboard, new cutting edge, scarifier, engine enclosures, 13.00-24 tyres. Machine is in very clean condition. Machine can be repainted in original Cat colors at extra cost. Rear ripper can be supplied at extra cost. Inspections are welcome. 15 units available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04762</title>
      <link>/stock/E04762/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04762/</guid>
      <description>New &amp;amp; Unused Ingersoll Rand Drilling Package, Ingersoll Rand ECM350 towed wagon drill, c/w IR DTH rotary head, can drill 85 mm to 127mm holes and capacity up to 150m deep, set up for down the hole (DTH) rotation drilling, 3,900 Nm Torque @ 8 bar 10,000LB pullback, takes 3.1mtr rods, rig weight 5,443 Kg, 300mm track shoes, manifold for water injection, safety check valves on main cylinders, Unused Doosan/Ingersoll-Rand SHP650 High Capacity Portable Air Compressor, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cummins 6CTA8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04769</title>
      <link>/stock/E04769/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04769/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7F Ex-Army dozer, sold new in 1998, only 527 hrs worked, O-rops cab, Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), Semi U-blade with tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, undercarriage on average 60% remaining, Hyster rear pulling winch. Machine can be supplied including independent Caterpillar TA inspection on request. Can be equipped with rear ripper and painted in Cat yellow at extra costs. Machine is in good and clean condition, inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04770</title>
      <link>/stock/E04770/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04770/</guid>
      <description>Fendt 260VA Vineyard tractor, 3 cylinder Deutz F3L913 engine, Rollbar, 4WD, powersteering, 3 point linkage EHR, PTO 540&amp;frasl;750 RPM, drawbar, toplink, hydr. spoolvalves, 280/70R16 front tyres and 360/70R24 rear tyres. Tractor comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04776</title>
      <link>/stock/E04776/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04776/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7F Ex-Army dozer, Only 147Hrs from new! O-rops cab with sweeps, Caterpillar 3306 engine with 200HP (149kW), Semi U-blade with tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, Hyster rear pulling winch, engine enclosures. Machine can be supplied including independent Caterpillar TA inspection and can be equipped with a rear ripper at extra costs. Machine is in good and clean condition, inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04778</title>
      <link>/stock/E04778/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04778/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D8R Dozer, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3406 engine with 320HP (235kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, differential steering, semi U-blade with tilt, 4-barrel single shank ripper with new wear parts, undercarriage average 80% remaining, 610mm shoes, front &amp;amp; rear work lights. Machine comes straight out of work, has new paint and is in clean condition. Independent Caterpillar TA inspection available on request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04779</title>
      <link>/stock/E04779/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04779/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D8R Dozer, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3406 engine with 320HP (235kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, differential steering, semi U-blade with tilt, new cutting edge fitted, 4-barrel single shank ripper with new wear parts, undercarriage average 80% remaining, 610mm shoes, front &amp;amp; rear work lights. Machine comes straight out of work, has new paint and is in clean condition. Independent Caterpillar TA inspection available on request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04781</title>
      <link>/stock/E04781/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04781/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7F Ex-Army dozer, O-rops cab, Caterpillar 3306 engine with 200HP (149kW), Semi U-blade with tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, Hyster rear pulling winch. Machine can be supplied including independent Caterpillar TA inspection and can be equipped with a rear ripper at extra costs. Machine is in good and clean condition, inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04785</title>
      <link>/stock/E04785/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04785/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D6K Series II LGP, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C6.6 ACERT Technology engine with 158HP (118kW), EPA certified, hydrostatic transmission, 6-way PAT blade, drawbar, extra valve for ripper, Grade Control, undercarriage on average 75% remaining, 760mm pads, front and rear work lights. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04787</title>
      <link>/stock/E04787/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04787/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D8T Dozer, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C15 ACERT Technology engine with 359HP (268kW), Tier 4 Interim, EPA, semi U-blade with tilt, new cutting edge fitted, Allied W12E rear pulling winch, ripper valve, differential steering, wrist control steering, front &amp;amp; rear work lights. Fully serviced and is in very clean condition. Inspections are welcome. Machine is available for sale or rent, subject to terms and conditions. Ripper available upon request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04788</title>
      <link>/stock/E04788/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04788/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D8T Dozer, E-rops cab with air conditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C15 ACERT Technology engine with 359HP (268kW), semi U-blade with tilt, new cutting edge fitted, blade width 3.95 Mtr, Allied W12E rear pulling winch, differential steering, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 610mm shoes, ripper valve, fast fill fuel kit. Machine comes straight out of work, is well maintained, has new paint and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04789</title>
      <link>/stock/E04789/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04789/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 330BL Excavator pipelayer, main machine sold new in 2002, converted into pipelayer in 2014, 3 units available, tipping point 65 ton, 7.3mtr. A-frame boom, Caterpillar 3306 engine, EPA Certified, 850mm triple grouser pads, cab with heater and airconditioning. Braden planetary dual brake lifting and deriking winch, 2 speed Rexroth hydr. piston motors, 19mm rope diameter, hydr. boom stop, anti-two block system, hydraulic joystick control, 3 side working range, can be transported in one load incl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04792</title>
      <link>/stock/E04792/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04792/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7G Ex-Army dozer, Delivered new in 2001, Only 554Hrs from new! O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, semi U blade with tilt, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 510mm pads, rear pulling winch, 22.500 Kgs operating weight. Rear ripper can be installed at extra cost. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome. Machine can be repainted in Cat yellow at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04793</title>
      <link>/stock/E04793/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04793/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7G Ex-Army dozer, Delivered new in 2010, Only 445Hrs from new! O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, semi U blade with tilt, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 610mm pads, rear pulling winch, 22.500 Kgs operating weight. Rear ripper can be installed at extra cost. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome. Machine can be repainted in Cat yellow at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04794</title>
      <link>/stock/E04794/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04794/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7G Ex-Army dozer, Delivered new in 2004, Only 744Hrs from new, O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, semi U blade with tilt, new cutting edge fitted, undercarriage on average 80% remaining, 510mm pads, rear pulling winch, 22.500 Kgs operating weight. Rear ripper can be installed at extra cost. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04795</title>
      <link>/stock/E04795/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04795/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7G Ex-Army dozer, Only 619Hrs from new, O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, semi U blade with tilt, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 510mm pads, multi shank rear ripper, 22.500 Kgs operating weight. Inspections are welcome. Machine comes straight out of work and is in very clean condition. Machine can be repainted in Cat yellow at extra cost. 8 units available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04796</title>
      <link>/stock/E04796/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04796/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7G Ex-Army dozer, Delivered new in 2007, Only 513Hrs from new! O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, semi U blade with tilt, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 510mm pads, rear pulling winch, 22.500 Kgs operating weight. Rear ripper can be installed at extra cost. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome. Machine can be repainted in Cat yellow at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04799</title>
      <link>/stock/E04799/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04799/</guid>
      <description>New &amp;amp; unused Xrok Transporter 6036T Mobile tracked stockpiling conveyor belt, powered by Caterpillar C2.2 engine with 49HP (36kW), 18 Mtr length, belt width 900mm, EP400 3 ply conveyor belt, galvanized inner legs, polyurethane belt scraper, remote greasing, hydraulic cylinders for raise and lower, CE marked. Delta Machinery is an authorized distributor for Xrok. Machines are available for sale or rent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04800</title>
      <link>/stock/E04800/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04800/</guid>
      <description>Komatsu WA350-3T, O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Komatsu SA6D108E-2 engine, 4 speed powershift transmission, bucket with teeth, work lights, engine enclosures, 20.5-25 tyres, lift cylinders are resealed. Repair pictures available on request. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04802</title>
      <link>/stock/E04802/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04802/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D8T Dozer, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C15 ACERT Technology engine with 359HP (268kW), semi U-blade with tilt, new cutting edge, 4 barrel SS-ripper with hydr. pin puller, differential steering, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, fast fill fuel system, brand new Caterpillar trackgroups fitted, 560mm shoes. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome. Full history available on request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04803</title>
      <link>/stock/E04803/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04803/</guid>
      <description>Unused Laurini PW400HY paywelder, canopy, joystick controlled hydrostatic transmission, Maxilift 040.3L crane class H2-B3, Mecc Alte generator 3 phase 400V, bottle rack, 570mm pads, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, CE marked. 3 Machines immediately available from stock. Available for sale or rent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04804</title>
      <link>/stock/E04804/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04804/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 320C LU, Cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Non-electronic Cat 3066TAA engine with 138HP (103kW), mono boom, 2.90 Mtr stick, hammer lines, GP bucket with teeth and side cutters, undercarriage on average 80% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04811</title>
      <link>/stock/E04811/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04811/</guid>
      <description>Komatsu WA200-6 Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 4 cylinder turbocharged Komatsu SAA4D107E-1 engine with 128HP (95kW), EPA Certified, 4 speed hydrostatic transmission, hydraulic quick release with bucket and forks, 20.5R25 tyres 80% remaining, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, engine enclosures. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04813</title>
      <link>/stock/E04813/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04813/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 320BL tracked excavator, cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3116 non-electronic engine with 128HP (96kW), mono boom, 2.90 Mtr stick, hammer lines, brand new GP bucket with teeth, undercarriage on average 70% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, work lights. Machine has been partially repainted and is in very clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04815</title>
      <link>/stock/E04815/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04815/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D9T, E-ROPS cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C18 ACERT Technology engine with 410HP (306kW), 3 speed powershift transmission which is overhauled recently, differential steering, wrist control steering, Fast Fill fuel system, Rebuild SS rear ripper with hydr. pin puller, all ripper cylinders resealed and new hoses, engine enclosures, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, undercarriage on average 85% remaining, 610mm single grouser shoes, 59.700Kgs operating weight, CE marked. New blade installed 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04819</title>
      <link>/stock/E04819/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04819/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7F Ex-Army dozer, Only 1697 Hrs from new! O-rops cab with sweeps, Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), Semi U-blade with tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, undercarriage on average 80% remaining, Hyster rear pulling winch. Machine can be supplied including independent Caterpillar TA inspection and can be equipped with a rear ripper at extra costs. Machine is in good and clean condition, inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04820</title>
      <link>/stock/E04820/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04820/</guid>
      <description>International 434 High Crop Tractor, 2WD, PTO, 13.6-28 rear tyres and 6.50-16 front tyres. Tractor comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Clearance underneath the tractor is 122 Cm, wheelspacing is 1.75 Mtr. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04830</title>
      <link>/stock/E04830/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04830/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 587R hydraulic operated pipelayers, delivered new in 2011, 8 units immediately available from stock The Netherlands, 91.625 kg lift capacity, 8.5 mtr boom (28ft) Paccar- Braden planetary winches, Free-fall function on hook line control, 2 speed Rexroth hydr. piston motors, 6 cylinder Caterpillar engine, Enclosed cab, 80% undercarriage, 864mm (34&amp;rdquo;) shoes, 3 speed powershift transmission, drawbar. Machines are in clean condition.
For sale and/or rental information please contact: Tel. +31 653 85 3392 or E-mail: John@deltamachinery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04837</title>
      <link>/stock/E04837/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04837/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 323D2L, Made in Japan, E-ROPS cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 158HP (118kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, 2.90 Mtr stick, hammer lines, GP bucket with new teeth (bucket width 1,12mtr), undercarriage on average 85% remaining, 600mm triple grouser shoes, rear &amp;amp; side view camera, work lights, 25.700 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine has low hours, comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04838</title>
      <link>/stock/E04838/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04838/</guid>
      <description>Doosan/Ingersoll-Rand XHP900WCAT High Capacity Portable Air Compressor, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 300HP (224kW), max. free air delivery 25.5 M3/Min (900 CFM), rated operating pressure 1.03 MPa (10.3 Bar), 7.50-16 tyres, operating weight 4.500 Kgs. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04846</title>
      <link>/stock/E04846/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04846/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7F Ex-Army dozer, Only 1422Hrs from new! O-rops cab, Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 189HP (141kW), Semi U-blade with tilt, new cutting edge, 3 speed powershift transmission, undercarriage on average 80% remaining, Hyster rear pulling winch. Machine can be supplied including independent Caterpillar TA inspection and can be equipped with a rear ripper at extra costs. Machine is in good and clean condition, inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04862</title>
      <link>/stock/E04862/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04862/</guid>
      <description>Hamm 311 Single drum vibrating roller, Canopy, 4 cylinder Cummins 4BTAA3.9-99C engine with 100HP (74kW), 2 speed hydrostatic transmission, 2 step vibrating, compaction meter, smooth drum, 23.1-26 tyres 90% remaining, operating weight 11.000 Kgs, front &amp;amp; rear work lights. Machine comes straight out of work, has low hours and is in very clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04863</title>
      <link>/stock/E04863/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04863/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D9R Dozer, Ex rental machine, Caterpillar 3408C Non-electronic engine with 443HP (330kW), E-Rops cab with airconditioning, Semi U-blade with tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, new 610mm single grouser pads fitted, single shank ripper, front and rear work lights. 2 units available for sale or rent, subject to terms and conditions. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04864</title>
      <link>/stock/E04864/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04864/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D9R Dozer, Ex rental machine, started working in 2015, Caterpillar 3408C Non-electronic engine with 443HP (330kW), E-Rops cab with airconditioning, Semi U-blade with tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, 685mm single grouser pads, single shank ripper, front and rear work lights. 2 units available for sale or rent, subject to terms and conditions. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04874</title>
      <link>/stock/E04874/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04874/</guid>
      <description>Brand new and unused Xrok Transporter 4030E Electric mobile stockpiling conveyor belts. 40ft (12mtr) x 30&amp;rdquo; (750mm). EP400 3 ply conveyor belt, galvanized inner legs, polyurethane belt scraper, feed boot extension, remote greasing, electric motor (5.5 kW) and gearbox combination unit, radial wheels, CE marked. Up to 200 TPH capacity! Always in stock! Delta Machinery is an authorized distributor for Xrok. Choice between 12mtr (40ft) until 24mtr (80ft), 750mm until 1000mm belts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04883</title>
      <link>/stock/E04883/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04883/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2 LME, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, hammer lines, Cat bucket with teeth, hydr. quick coupler, undercarriage 80% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, work lights, 39.400 Kgs operating weight, rear view camera, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04888</title>
      <link>/stock/E04888/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04888/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 330D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 208HP (155kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.65 Mtr, Caterpillar GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 60&amp;rdquo; (1.50mtr), CB linkage family, hammer lines, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, 33.000 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04889</title>
      <link>/stock/E04889/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04889/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 330D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 208HP (155kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.65 Mtr, Caterpillar GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 60&amp;rdquo; (1.50mtr), CB linkage family, hammer lines, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, 33.000 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04890</title>
      <link>/stock/E04890/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04890/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 330D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 208HP (155kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.65 Mtr, Caterpillar GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 60&amp;rdquo; (1.50mtr), CB linkage family, hammer lines, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear view camera, work lights, 33.000 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04891</title>
      <link>/stock/E04891/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04891/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 330D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 208HP (155kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.65 Mtr, Caterpillar GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 60&amp;rdquo; (1.50mtr), CB linkage family, hammer lines, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear view camera, work lights, 33.000 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04892</title>
      <link>/stock/E04892/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04892/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 330D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 208HP (155kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.65 Mtr, Caterpillar GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 60&amp;rdquo; (1.50mtr), CB linkage family, hammer lines, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear view camera, work lights, 33.000 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04893</title>
      <link>/stock/E04893/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04893/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 330D2L, Made in Japan, Delivered new in 2017, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 208HP (155kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.65 Mtr, Caterpillar GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 60&amp;rdquo; (1.50mtr), CB linkage family, hammer lines, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, 33.000 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04894</title>
      <link>/stock/E04894/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04894/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 330D2L, Made in Japan, Delivered new in 2017, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 208HP (155kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.65 Mtr, Caterpillar GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 60&amp;rdquo; (1.50mtr), CB linkage family, hammer lines, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, 33.000 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04895</title>
      <link>/stock/E04895/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04895/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, central lubrication system, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04896</title>
      <link>/stock/E04896/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04896/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04897</title>
      <link>/stock/E04897/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04897/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, Delivered new in 2018, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04899</title>
      <link>/stock/E04899/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04899/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, central lubrication system, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04900</title>
      <link>/stock/E04900/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04900/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04901</title>
      <link>/stock/E04901/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04901/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04902</title>
      <link>/stock/E04902/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04902/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04903</title>
      <link>/stock/E04903/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04903/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, front cab guard, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, hammer lines, hydraulic quick coupler, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04904</title>
      <link>/stock/E04904/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04904/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, front cab guard, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, hammer lines, hydraulic quick coupler, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04905</title>
      <link>/stock/E04905/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04905/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, front cab guard, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, hammer lines, hydraulic quick coupler, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04906</title>
      <link>/stock/E04906/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04906/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, front cab guard, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, hammer lines, hydraulic quick coupler, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04907</title>
      <link>/stock/E04907/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04907/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04908</title>
      <link>/stock/E04908/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04908/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04910</title>
      <link>/stock/E04910/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04910/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, central lubrication system, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04911</title>
      <link>/stock/E04911/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04911/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, cab guard, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04912</title>
      <link>/stock/E04912/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04912/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04913</title>
      <link>/stock/E04913/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04913/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04914</title>
      <link>/stock/E04914/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04914/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04915</title>
      <link>/stock/E04915/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04915/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, Delivered new in 2018, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04916</title>
      <link>/stock/E04916/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04916/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, front cab guard, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.30 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04917</title>
      <link>/stock/E04917/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04917/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04918</title>
      <link>/stock/E04918/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04918/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04919</title>
      <link>/stock/E04919/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04919/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, front cab guard, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04920</title>
      <link>/stock/E04920/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04920/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04921</title>
      <link>/stock/E04921/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04921/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 980H Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C15 ACERT Technology engine with 348HP (260kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, V-rock bucket with teeth, ride control, Command Control Steering, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, 29.5R25 tyres, 31.330 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04924</title>
      <link>/stock/E04924/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04924/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 980H Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C15 ACERT Technology engine with 348HP (260kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, V-rock bucket with teeth, ride control, Command Control Steering, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, 29.5R25 tyres, 31.330 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04925</title>
      <link>/stock/E04925/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04925/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 950GC Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 225HP (168kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, Full steer, GP bucket with teeth, bucket capacity 3.30 M3, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, 23.5R25 tyres, 18.100 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04926</title>
      <link>/stock/E04926/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04926/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 950GC Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 225HP (168kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, Full steer, GP bucket with teeth, bucket capacity 3.30 M3, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, 23.5R25 tyres, 18.100 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04929</title>
      <link>/stock/E04929/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04929/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 434F2 Backhoe loader, Made in UK, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 4 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C4.4 engine with 101HP (75kW), 6 speed Auto-Shift transmission 40 KM/H, 4WD, All Wheel Steer, multipurpose 4-in-1 bucket with teeth, extendable backhoe stick, side shift frame, GP bucket with teeth, extra auxiliary function, 2 hydraulic stabilizers, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, operating weight 9.130 Kgs, 440&amp;frasl;80-28 tyres, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04930</title>
      <link>/stock/E04930/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04930/</guid>
      <description>New Holland TS115, cab, 6 cylinder NH engine with 106HP (79kW), 4WD, 16F-16R Electroshift transmission, 3-point hitch, front hitch, PTO, hydraulic spoolvalves, work lights, 420/85R38 rear tyres and 340/85R28 front tyres. Tractor comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04939</title>
      <link>/stock/E04939/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04939/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7G Ex-Army dozer, Delivered new in 2004, Only 659Hrs from new! O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, semi U blade with tilt, undercarriage on average 75% remaining, 510mm pads, rear pulling winch, 22.500 Kgs operating weight. Rear ripper can be installed at extra cost. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome. Machine can be repainted in Cat yellow at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04940</title>
      <link>/stock/E04940/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04940/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7G Ex-Army dozer, Delivered new in 2004, Only 900Hrs from new! O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, semi U blade with tilt, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 510mm pads, rear pulling winch, 22.500 Kgs operating weight. Rear ripper can be installed at extra cost. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome. Machine can be repainted in Cat yellow at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04943</title>
      <link>/stock/E04943/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04943/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D6R XL, E-rops cab with air conditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat 3306DI engine with 185HP (138kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, differential steering, wrist control steering, A blade with double tilt (not shown on picture), new cutting edge, 610mm shoes, front and rear work lights, engine enclosures, drawbar, rear view camera, operating weight 19.000 Kgs, new carrier rollers and sprockets fitted, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04944</title>
      <link>/stock/E04944/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04944/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 322CL, FOPS Cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat 3126B ATAAC engine with 165HP (123kW), cab guard, mono boom, Smartboom, check valves, stick length 2.95 Mtr, hammer lines, extra aux. hydr. function, hydr. quick coupler, GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 1.41 Mtr, undercarriage average 70% remaining, 700mm triple grouser pads, 26.903 Kgs operating weight, work lights, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work, inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04951</title>
      <link>/stock/E04951/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04951/</guid>
      <description>Very rare Massey Ferguson 240 with 4WD, Power steering, Lambourn cab, 3 cylinder Perkins engine with 41HP (55kW), 3-point hitch, PTO, hydr. spoolvalves, 30% 14.9-28 rear tyres and 50% 8.3&amp;frasl;8-24 front tyres 50%. Tractor comes straight out of work, inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04952</title>
      <link>/stock/E04952/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04952/</guid>
      <description>Massey Ferguson 2640, cab with heater, 6 cylinder turbocharged engine with 135HP (99kW), 4WD, 16F-12R transmission, 3-point linkage, toplink, PTO, front hitch, front PTO, hydraulic spoolvalves, drawbar, Michelin Multibib 480/65R28 front tyres, Klber 600/65R38 rear tyres, front &amp;amp; rear work lights. Tractor comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04953</title>
      <link>/stock/E04953/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04953/</guid>
      <description>Brand new and unused Xrok Transporter 5030E Electric mobile stockpiling conveyor belts. 50ft (15mtr) x 30&amp;rdquo; (750mm). EP400 3 ply conveyor belt, galvanized inner legs, polyurethane belt scraper, feed boot extension, remote greasing, electric motor (5.5 kW) and gearbox combination unit, radial wheels, CE marked. Up to 200 TPH capacity! Always in stock! Delta Machinery is an authorized distributor for Xrok. Choice between 12mtr (40ft) until 24mtr (80ft), 750mm until 1000mm belts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04954</title>
      <link>/stock/E04954/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04954/</guid>
      <description>Brand new and unused Xrok Transporter 6030E Electric mobile stockpiling conveyor belts. 60ft (18mtr) x 30&amp;rdquo; (750mm). EP400 3 ply conveyor belt, galvanized inner legs, polyurethane belt scraper, feed boot extension, remote greasing, electric motor (5.5 kW) and gearbox combination unit, radial wheels, CE marked. Up to 200 TPH capacity! Always in stock! Delta Machinery is an authorized distributor for Xrok. Choice between 12mtr (40ft) until 24mtr (80ft), 750mm until 1000mm belts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04955</title>
      <link>/stock/E04955/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04955/</guid>
      <description>Brand new and unused Xrok Transporter 8030E Electric mobile stockpiling conveyor belts. 80ft (24mtr) x 30&amp;rdquo; (750mm). EP400 3 ply conveyor belt, galvanized inner legs, polyurethane belt scraper, feed boot extension, remote greasing, electric motor (7.0 kW) and gearbox combination unit, radial wheels, CE marked. Up to 200 TPH capacity! Always in stock! Delta Machinery is an authorized distributor for Xrok. Choice between 12mtr (40ft) until 24mtr (80ft), 750mm until 1000mm belts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04964</title>
      <link>/stock/E04964/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04964/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Xrok Rotator 380 Recycling Screen available in a tracked or wheeled configuration. Delta Machinery is an authorized distributor for Xrok. Machine is available for sale or rent. Inspections are welcome. Demonstration available. For more info please call +31 888 966 966 or email us at: sales@deltamachinery.nl You can also visit the XROK website: www.xrok.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04966</title>
      <link>/stock/E04966/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04966/</guid>
      <description>Xrok Transporter 5036T Mobile tracked stockpiling conveyor belt, powered by Caterpillar C2.2 engine with 49HP (36kW), 15 Mtr length, belt width 900mm, EP400 3 ply conveyor belt, galvanized inner legs, polyurethane belt scraper, remote greasing, hydraulic cylinders for raise and lower, undercarriage 75% remaining, 400mm pads, CE marked. Delta Machinery is an authorized distributor for Xrok. Inspections are welcome. New Xrok stockpiling conveyor belts available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04982</title>
      <link>/stock/E04982/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04982/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D6R Series II, E-rops cab with air conditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 185HP (138kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, semi U-blade with tilt, new cutting edge fitted, differential steering, wrist control steering, undercarriage on average 80% remaining, 610mm shoes, rear view camera, drawbar, front and rear work lights, operating weight 19.000 Kgs. CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04983</title>
      <link>/stock/E04983/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04983/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D6R XL Series II, E-rops cab with air conditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 185HP (138kW), EPA certified, 3 speed powershift transmission, semi U-blade with tilt, differential steering, wrist control steering, undercarriage on average 75% remaining, 610mm shoes, rear view camera, drawbar, front and rear work lights, operating weight 19.000 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04994</title>
      <link>/stock/E04994/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04994/</guid>
      <description>New and Unused Alpsan SCP329 Semi-lowbed trailer, 3 Axles, 12 Ton axles, gross weight 54 Ton, length 14.2 Mtr, width 2.55 Mtr, load platform length 8.9 Mtr, air suspension, dual tyres, one lift axle, 275/70R22.5 tyres, electro-hydraulic ramps, EBS air brake system, side extensions (300mm), 50mm thickness hard wooden floor and steel covered over tyres, CE marked. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04995</title>
      <link>/stock/E04995/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04995/</guid>
      <description>New and Unused GT Extendable semi-lowbed trailer, 4 axles, 12 Ton axles, gross weight 71 Ton, length 14 Mtr + 6 Mtr extendable, width 2.55 Mtr, load platform length 10 Mtr, 3 hydraulic steering axles, one lift axle, air suspension, dual tyres, 2 hydraulic outriggers, 235/75R17.5 tyres, side extensions (300mm), twist locks for 2 x 20 ft / 1 x 40 ft container, 2 wide storage boxes underneath, EBS air brake system, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04996</title>
      <link>/stock/E04996/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04996/</guid>
      <description>New and Unused Scorpion SCP329 Semi-lowbed trailer, 3 Axles, 12 Ton axles, gross weight 54 Ton, length 14.2 Mtr, width 3.0 Mtr, load platform length 8.85 Mtr, steel suspension, dual tyres, one lift axle, 275/70R22.5 tyres, electro-hydraulic ramps, EBS air brake system, side extensions (300mm), 50mm thickness hard wooden floor and steel covered over tyres, CE marked. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K00003</title>
      <link>/stock/K00003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K00003/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 3406PCTA engine, 360HP @ 2100RPM. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K00004</title>
      <link>/stock/K00004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K00004/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 3406B engine, arrangement number 7C-6842, for parts or repair. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K00006</title>
      <link>/stock/K00006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K00006/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 3406 turbocharged engine, including ECM, engine does not run. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K00008</title>
      <link>/stock/K00008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K00008/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 3406B turbocharged engine, engine does not run. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K00106</title>
      <link>/stock/K00106/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K00106/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 3406B turbocharged engine, arrangement number 4W-3607, engine does not run. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K00109</title>
      <link>/stock/K00109/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K00109/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 3406 turbocharged engine, including ECM, engine does not run. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K00388</title>
      <link>/stock/K00388/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K00388/</guid>
      <description>DNB D 90lls, Rated for excavators from 18 till 30 ton, 1860 kgs operating weight, oil flow 120-160 L/min, 140 bar operating pressure, 350-500 blows/min impact frequency, 4400 Joules impact energy, 130mm tool diameter. Hammer is ex job site condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K00576</title>
      <link>/stock/K00576/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K00576/</guid>
      <description>Parker Kubitizer, 10pcs available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K00654</title>
      <link>/stock/K00654/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K00654/</guid>
      <description>Unused Parker 700x450 wedge set. 5 sets available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K00699</title>
      <link>/stock/K00699/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K00699/</guid>
      <description>Unused Terex-Pegson 11650 / XA400 fixed jaw plate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K00723</title>
      <link>/stock/K00723/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K00723/</guid>
      <description>Miller Rock hammer Bracket to suit Caterpillar 345 or similar size excavator, pins 90/110mm, stick 505mm, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K00781</title>
      <link>/stock/K00781/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K00781/</guid>
      <description>Unused Extec T9750D 3 axle bogie for Extec C12 or similar size jaw crusher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K00783</title>
      <link>/stock/K00783/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K00783/</guid>
      <description>Unused Extec T9750D 3 axle bogie for Extec C12 or similar size jaw crusher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K00786</title>
      <link>/stock/K00786/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K00786/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 3304PC, no fuel pump. Engine does not run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K00798</title>
      <link>/stock/K00798/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K00798/</guid>
      <description>Ripper to fit Komatsu D65 or similar size dozer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K00899</title>
      <link>/stock/K00899/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K00899/</guid>
      <description>Mobile storage tank, 27000 ltr capacity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K00900</title>
      <link>/stock/K00900/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K00900/</guid>
      <description>Mobile storage tank, 27000 ltr capacity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01008</title>
      <link>/stock/K01008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01008/</guid>
      <description>Final drive assembly to suit Caterpillar 320C/CL excavator. Part is inspected and is in very good and clean condition. Cat partno: 227-6035</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01010</title>
      <link>/stock/K01010/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01010/</guid>
      <description>Hydraulic travel motor to suit Cat 320C/CL excavator. Part is inspected and is in very good and clean condition. Cat partno: 107-7029</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01011</title>
      <link>/stock/K01011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01011/</guid>
      <description>Hydraulic travel motor to suit Cat 320C/CL excavator. Part is inspected and is in very good and clean condition. Cat partno: 107-7029</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01012</title>
      <link>/stock/K01012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01012/</guid>
      <description>Complete hydraulic main valve group to suit Cat 320C/CL excavator. Part is inspected and is in very good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01049</title>
      <link>/stock/K01049/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01049/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 3176B engine, 6 cylinder turbocharged engine with 275HP (205kW) @ 1800RPM, arrangement number 6I-2641</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01361</title>
      <link>/stock/K01361/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01361/</guid>
      <description>Sauer Danfoss 90R130 KP5CD80 axial piston pump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01384</title>
      <link>/stock/K01384/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01384/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 3406 engine, engine does not run. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01438</title>
      <link>/stock/K01438/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01438/</guid>
      <description>New toggle seat for Terex-Pegson 11650 jaw crusher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01443</title>
      <link>/stock/K01443/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01443/</guid>
      <description>Unused Terex-Pegson 11650 Lower cheek plate LH</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01444</title>
      <link>/stock/K01444/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01444/</guid>
      <description>Unused Terex-Pegson 11650 Lower cheek plate RH</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01468</title>
      <link>/stock/K01468/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01468/</guid>
      <description>Cummins model HB, 6 cylinder diesel engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01593</title>
      <link>/stock/K01593/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01593/</guid>
      <description>Fuel tank to suit Caterpillar TH360B telehandler, including hoses, Caterpillar part number 224-4783. Tank is in very good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01599</title>
      <link>/stock/K01599/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01599/</guid>
      <description>Unused 2012 Delta DM120 mobile power pack, 5HP (3.8KW) vertical shaft Briggs and Stratton Engine, Saturn 5 GPM hydr. pump, operating pressure; 120 bar, (1750PSI) 37.8 L/pm at 3000 RPM, max. pressure 200 Bar, (2900 PSI) manual operated 2 way relieve valve. P1-P2=3&amp;frasl;8&amp;rdquo;, T1=1&amp;frasl;2&amp;rdquo;, T2=3&amp;frasl;8&amp;rdquo;, A,B= 3&amp;frasl;8&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01670</title>
      <link>/stock/K01670/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01670/</guid>
      <description>8pcs New carrier roller shells to fit Komatsu D85-21, Komatsu part number 154-30-25111E. Genuine Komatsu parts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01718</title>
      <link>/stock/K01718/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01718/</guid>
      <description>Unused factory built 14m x 900mm mobile feed conveyor complete with intergrated feed hopper. c/w single axle trailer. Suitable for feeding cone crusher or screen plant. Belt discharge height in working position 6.75 Mtr, Hopper length 4.0 Mtr, Hopper width 1.9 Mtr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01732</title>
      <link>/stock/K01732/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01732/</guid>
      <description>Geith ditch cleaning bucket, width 182Cm, new cutting edge, pin diameter 80mm, distance between hinges 330mm. Bucket is in very good condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01739</title>
      <link>/stock/K01739/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01739/</guid>
      <description>Scott ditch cleaning bucket, width 213Cm, pin diameter 80mm, distance between hinges 305mm, weld on cutting edge. Bucket is in good condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01742</title>
      <link>/stock/K01742/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01742/</guid>
      <description>Ditch cleaning bucket, width 211Cm, pin diameter 80mm, distance between hinges 305mm, weld on cutting edge. Bucket is in good condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01918</title>
      <link>/stock/K01918/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01918/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Lincoln Invertec V-350 PRO welding machine. 2 units available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K01919</title>
      <link>/stock/K01919/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K01919/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Lincoln Invertec V-350 PRO welding machine. 2 units available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02004</title>
      <link>/stock/K02004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02004/</guid>
      <description>Brand new Caterpillar trackguards to suit Cat excavators, several models available, additional information on request. Part numbers 192-8303 / 157-1606 / 7Y-2581</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02005</title>
      <link>/stock/K02005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02005/</guid>
      <description>Brand new Caterpillar trackguards to suit Cat excavators, several models available, additional information on request. Part numbers 192-8303 / 157-1606 / 7Y-2581</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02197</title>
      <link>/stock/K02197/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02197/</guid>
      <description>O-ROPS cab to suit Caterpillar 140G/140H motorgrader. Rops is in clean and straight condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02198</title>
      <link>/stock/K02198/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02198/</guid>
      <description>O-ROPS cab to suit Caterpillar 140G/140H motorgrader. Rops is in clean and straight condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02244</title>
      <link>/stock/K02244/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02244/</guid>
      <description>Swivel GP to suit Cat 365BL excavator, Cat part number 156-0622.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02262</title>
      <link>/stock/K02262/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02262/</guid>
      <description>Fuel tank GP to suit Cat 365BL excavator, Cat part number 138-5596.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02263</title>
      <link>/stock/K02263/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02263/</guid>
      <description>Hydraulic oil tank GP to suit Cat 365BL excavator, Cat part number 152-9339.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02264</title>
      <link>/stock/K02264/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02264/</guid>
      <description>Storage box GP to suit Cat 365BL excavator, Cat part number 170-2808.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02265</title>
      <link>/stock/K02265/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02265/</guid>
      <description>Unused Mandingers forkframe, FEM3, c/w hydr. side-shift cylinder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02287</title>
      <link>/stock/K02287/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02287/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 1693 diesel engine, 6 cylinder turbocharged. Engine does not run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02290</title>
      <link>/stock/K02290/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02290/</guid>
      <description>Iveco 6 cylinder turbocharged diesel engine, 24 valve, commonrail fuel system, c/w engine ECM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02300</title>
      <link>/stock/K02300/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02300/</guid>
      <description>Tighe top plate for rock hammer, suitable for excavators from 45 - 50 Ton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02313</title>
      <link>/stock/K02313/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02313/</guid>
      <description>Cummins L10, 6 cylinder turbocharged engine with 300HP (224kW) @ 2100RPM, 10.0 Ltr displacement, engine is fully rebuild by Cummins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02338</title>
      <link>/stock/K02338/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02338/</guid>
      <description>Cab to suit Caterpillar D7G or similar size dozer. Cab is straight and is in clean condition. 4 units immediately available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02364</title>
      <link>/stock/K02364/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02364/</guid>
      <description>Edwards Truecut 3.25/2500DD guillotine shear, max capacity 2535x3.25mm (99.5x10BG inch), front support arms, rigid one piece all steel construction, shrouded foot control unit, 7.5kW motor, 3 phase 420V.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02417</title>
      <link>/stock/K02417/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02417/</guid>
      <description>Atlas-Copco TEROC 991 bit grinder, max working pressure 7 bar, max 18.000RPM, made in Sweden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02429</title>
      <link>/stock/K02429/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02429/</guid>
      <description>Set used drill rods for Terex-Halco rock drill, 75mm diameter, 3 Mtr length, 7 pieces. Drills are straight and in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02450</title>
      <link>/stock/K02450/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02450/</guid>
      <description>Brand new Delta DLG980G log fork for wheelloader. Specially designed to comfortably and safely handle most severe logging applications. The tines are made of Hardox steel for maximum strength and excellent resistance to impact and abrasion. Custom build options are available for any brand and type of wheel loader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02492</title>
      <link>/stock/K02492/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02492/</guid>
      <description>GP bucket with teeth to suit Cat 330D or similar size excavator, width 68Cm, pin diameter 100mm - 90mm, distance between hinges 390mm, including pins. Bucket is in excellent condition and has new paint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02510</title>
      <link>/stock/K02510/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02510/</guid>
      <description>Overhauled hydraulic lift cylinder to suit Volvo L330E wheelloader, new rod + seals fitted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02886</title>
      <link>/stock/K02886/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02886/</guid>
      <description>Site safe Steel Tool chest, lockable lid, yellow colour, forklift pockets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02887</title>
      <link>/stock/K02887/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02887/</guid>
      <description>Steel toolbox, lockable lid, green color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02899</title>
      <link>/stock/K02899/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02899/</guid>
      <description>Brand new FG Wilson generator sub frame with integrated fuel tank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02931</title>
      <link>/stock/K02931/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02931/</guid>
      <description>Brand new Delta DLG420 log fork for wheelloader. Specially designed to comfortably and safely handle most severe logging applications. The tines are made of Hardox steel for maximum strength and excellent resistance to impact and abrasion. Custom build options are available for any brand and type of wheel loader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02966</title>
      <link>/stock/K02966/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02966/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Drill rods (9 pcs) to suit Ingersoll-Rand / Atlas Copco rock drills, length 310 Cm, diameter 76mm, thread 2 3&amp;frasl;8&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02967</title>
      <link>/stock/K02967/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02967/</guid>
      <description>Counterweight to fit Caterpillar D7R dozer, genuine Caterpillar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03025</title>
      <link>/stock/K03025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03025/</guid>
      <description>Geith ditch cleaning bucket, width 244Cm, bolt on cutting edge, pin diameter 80mm, distance between hinges 350mm. Bucket is in good condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03055</title>
      <link>/stock/K03055/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03055/</guid>
      <description>O-ROPS cab to suit Caterpillar D9H dozer. Rops is in very good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03056</title>
      <link>/stock/K03056/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03056/</guid>
      <description>Genuine Caterpillar SS parallelogram ripper to suit Cat D9H dozer, hydraulic cylinders are resealed, c/w brackets, pins and control valves, excluding shank. Ripper is complete and is in very good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03084</title>
      <link>/stock/K03084/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03084/</guid>
      <description>Brand new and unused Terex-Pegson flywheel to suit 11650&amp;frasl;11800 crusher, outside diameter 1270mm, inside diameter 190mm, width 405mm, 1x grove + 1x smooth flywheel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03085</title>
      <link>/stock/K03085/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03085/</guid>
      <description>Brand new and unused Terex-Pegson flywheel to suit 11650&amp;frasl;11800 crusher, outside diameter 1270mm, inside diameter 190mm, width 405mm, 1x grove + 1x smooth flywheel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03088</title>
      <link>/stock/K03088/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03088/</guid>
      <description>Terex-Pegson Trakpactor 428&amp;frasl;320 hammer, part number 6984&amp;frasl;79. Several pieces available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03095</title>
      <link>/stock/K03095/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03095/</guid>
      <description>New Timken bearing to suit Terex Pegson 1000 cone crusher, part number NP389735-902A1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03096</title>
      <link>/stock/K03096/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03096/</guid>
      <description>New Timken bearing to suit Terex Pegson 1000 cone crusher, part number NP389735-902A1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03116</title>
      <link>/stock/K03116/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03116/</guid>
      <description>Hydraulic lift cylinder RH side to suit Cat D9H dozer. Part is in good and clean condition. Cat partno: 3G-1176</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03117</title>
      <link>/stock/K03117/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03117/</guid>
      <description>Hydraulic lift cylinder LH side to suit Cat D9H dozer. Part is in good and clean condition. Cat partno: 3G-1177</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03119</title>
      <link>/stock/K03119/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03119/</guid>
      <description>Genuine Caterpillar SS ripper to suit Cat D9H dozer, c/w brackets, pins and control valves, hydr. pin puller, including shank. Ripper is complete and is in very good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03132</title>
      <link>/stock/K03132/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03132/</guid>
      <description>Brand new and unused SEC excavator ripper to suit Caterpillar 330DL or similar size excavator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03134</title>
      <link>/stock/K03134/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03134/</guid>
      <description>NPK H30X Rockhammer, rated for excavators from 50-75 ton, 4.808 Kgs operating weight, oil flow 250-303 L/min, 183 bar operating pressure, 300-350 blows/min impact frequency, 175mm tool diameter, including chisel. Hydraulic hoses and adapter plate can be supplied at extra cost. Hammer is in ex-job site condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03136</title>
      <link>/stock/K03136/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03136/</guid>
      <description>Unused Mustang MB1500 hammer, working pressure 150 bar, oil flow 100-145 Ltr/min, relief pressure 250 bar, operating weight 1500 Kgs, conical chisel, 130mm tool diameter, 400-900 blows/min impact frequency, CE marked. Rated for excavators from 18 till 26 ton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03178</title>
      <link>/stock/K03178/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03178/</guid>
      <description>O-ROPS cab to suit Caterpillar D9H dozer. Rops is in very good and clean condition. Sweeps not available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03182</title>
      <link>/stock/K03182/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03182/</guid>
      <description>Hydraulic lift cylinder LH side to suit Cat D9H dozer. Part is in good and clean condition. Cat partno: 3G-1177</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03183</title>
      <link>/stock/K03183/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03183/</guid>
      <description>Hydraulic lift cylinder RH side to suit Cat D9H dozer. Part is in good and clean condition. Cat partno: 3G-1176</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03186</title>
      <link>/stock/K03186/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03186/</guid>
      <description>Drawbar to fit Cat D7F/D7G dozer, genuine Caterpillar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03187</title>
      <link>/stock/K03187/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03187/</guid>
      <description>Drawbar to fit Cat D7F/D7G dozer, genuine Caterpillar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03340</title>
      <link>/stock/K03340/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03340/</guid>
      <description>Allied W8L winch to suit dozer, maximum rated line pull 36.287 Kgs (80.000 lbs), good cable, c/w drive shaft and build-in drawbar, SCH oil brake. Suitable for Caterpillar D7, D8, Komatsu D85 / D155, Dressta TD20, New Holland D255 or similar size dozer. Winch is in very good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03390</title>
      <link>/stock/K03390/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03390/</guid>
      <description>E-rops cab to suit Komatsu D355 dozer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03391</title>
      <link>/stock/K03391/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03391/</guid>
      <description>O-rops to suit Cat 980 wheel loader, original Caterpillar in good condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03392</title>
      <link>/stock/K03392/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03392/</guid>
      <description>O-rops to suit Cat 815B compactor, original Caterpillar in good condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03393</title>
      <link>/stock/K03393/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03393/</guid>
      <description>O-rops cab to suit Cat D7H dozer, original Caterpillar in good condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03394</title>
      <link>/stock/K03394/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03394/</guid>
      <description>O-rops cab to suit Cat D8N dozer, original Caterpillar in good condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03395</title>
      <link>/stock/K03395/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03395/</guid>
      <description>O-rops cab to suit Cat D4H dozer, original Caterpillar ROPS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03396</title>
      <link>/stock/K03396/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03396/</guid>
      <description>O-rops cab to suit Komatsu D155 dozer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03408</title>
      <link>/stock/K03408/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03408/</guid>
      <description>Brand new and unused complete multi shank ripper to suit Cat D7G/F dozer, c/w 3 shanks. Ripper is complete including hydr. cylinders / 3 shanks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03421</title>
      <link>/stock/K03421/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03421/</guid>
      <description>Unused Caterpillar D9H track shoes, width 30&amp;rdquo; (760mm), single grouser, full set 78pcs. Track bolts/nuts can be supplied at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03423</title>
      <link>/stock/K03423/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03423/</guid>
      <description>Scott ditch cleaning bucket, width 243Cm, pin diameter 90mm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03427</title>
      <link>/stock/K03427/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03427/</guid>
      <description>NPK E220 Rockhammer, rated for excavators from 30-45 ton, 3.085 Kgs operating weight, oil flow 200-250 L/min, 162 bar operating pressure, 350-430 blows/min impact frequency, 156mm tool diameter, including chisel. Hydraulic hoses and adapter plate can be supplied at extra cost. Hammer is in good condition, test movie available on request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03444</title>
      <link>/stock/K03444/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03444/</guid>
      <description>Carco 120 winch to suit Caterpillar D8K dozer, Ex-army. Winch is in good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03449</title>
      <link>/stock/K03449/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03449/</guid>
      <description>WEG electric motor, 315KW, 50 Herz, CE marked. Motor is tested and is in good condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03526</title>
      <link>/stock/K03526/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03526/</guid>
      <description>Remanufactured Cat hydraulic/steering piston pump gp to suit Cat 12H/120H/140H/160H motor grader, part number 10R-2511 (169-4882). Outright sale only!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03531</title>
      <link>/stock/K03531/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03531/</guid>
      <description>Mantle to suit Metso LT200 / HP200 cone (18% Chrome, 2% Manganese) . Metso Part No 1050130813</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03532</title>
      <link>/stock/K03532/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03532/</guid>
      <description>Mantle to suit Metso LT200 / HP200 cone (18% Chrome, 2% Manganese) . Metso Part No 1050130813</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03533</title>
      <link>/stock/K03533/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03533/</guid>
      <description>Mantle to suit Metso LT200 / HP200 cone (18% Chrome, 2% Manganese) . Metso Part No 1050130813</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03548</title>
      <link>/stock/K03548/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03548/</guid>
      <description>Unused Cat hydraulic/steering piston pump gp to suit Cat 12H/120H/140H/160H motor grader, part number 169-4882 (10R-2511). Outright sale only!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03549</title>
      <link>/stock/K03549/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03549/</guid>
      <description>Remanufactured Cat hydraulic fan piston pump gp to suit Cat 12H/120H/140H/160H motor grader, part number 10R-3805 (169-4883). Outright sale only!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03579</title>
      <link>/stock/K03579/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03579/</guid>
      <description>Set of 4pcs new &amp;amp; unused high chrome blow bars to suit Terex-Pegson 1412 / XA500 Trakpactor crusher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03580</title>
      <link>/stock/K03580/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03580/</guid>
      <description>Set of 4pcs new &amp;amp; unused high chrome blow bars to suit Terex-Pegson 1412 / XA500 Trakpactor crusher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03620</title>
      <link>/stock/K03620/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03620/</guid>
      <description>New manufactured subframe structure for large Jaw Crusher (up to 1200x800 size) including rock box, flywheel guards, safety walkways, laders and handrails, 132kw electric motor complete with adjustment bracket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03622</title>
      <link>/stock/K03622/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03622/</guid>
      <description>Drawbar to fit Komatsu D65EX-16 / D65PX-16 / D65WX-16 dozer, genuine Komatsu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03635</title>
      <link>/stock/K03635/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03635/</guid>
      <description>Counterweight to suit Hitachi excavator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03716</title>
      <link>/stock/K03716/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03716/</guid>
      <description>Ditch cleaning bucket with cutting edge, width 210 Cm, pin diameter 80mm, dipper 310mm, centres 445mm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03729</title>
      <link>/stock/K03729/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03729/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Boart Longyear PLA201.1 pneumatic jack hammer. 5 units immediately available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03735</title>
      <link>/stock/K03735/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03735/</guid>
      <description>New and unused ABB electric motor, type M3AA250SMA4, 55kW, 60Hz, 1783 RPM, shaft diameter 65mm, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03736</title>
      <link>/stock/K03736/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03736/</guid>
      <description>New and unused ABB electric motor, type M3AA250SMB4, 75kW, 60Hz, 1780 RPM, shaft diameter 65mm, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03739</title>
      <link>/stock/K03739/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03739/</guid>
      <description>New and unused ABB electric motor, type M2AA160MLA4, 11kW, 50Hz, 1459 RPM, shaft diameter 42mm, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03740</title>
      <link>/stock/K03740/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03740/</guid>
      <description>New and unused ABB electric motor, type M3AA250SMC, 95kW, 50Hz, 1477 RPM, shaft diameter 65mm, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03742</title>
      <link>/stock/K03742/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03742/</guid>
      <description>New and unused ABB electric motor, type M3AA250SMC4, 95kW, 50Hz, 1478 RPM, shaft diameter 65mm, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03744</title>
      <link>/stock/K03744/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03744/</guid>
      <description>New and unused ABB electric motor, type M2AA160MLA4, 11kW, 50Hz, 1459 RPM, shaft diameter 42mm, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03745</title>
      <link>/stock/K03745/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03745/</guid>
      <description>New and unused ABB electric motor, type M2AA160MLA4, 11kW, 50Hz, 1459 RPM, shaft diameter 42mm, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03746</title>
      <link>/stock/K03746/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03746/</guid>
      <description>New and unused ABB electric motor, type M2AA160MLA4, 11kW, 50Hz, 1459 RPM, shaft diameter 42mm, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03747</title>
      <link>/stock/K03747/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03747/</guid>
      <description>New and unused ABB electric motor, type M3AA250SMC, 75kW, 50Hz, 1485 RPM, shaft diameter 54mm, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03748</title>
      <link>/stock/K03748/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03748/</guid>
      <description>New and unused ABB electric motor, type M2AA160MLA4, 11kW, 50Hz, 1459 RPM, shaft diameter 42mm, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03749</title>
      <link>/stock/K03749/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03749/</guid>
      <description>New and unused ABB electric motor, type M2CA315SMA 4 IMB35/IM2001, 132kW, 50Hz, 1486 RPM, shaft diameter 80mm, CE marked. Atlas Copco part number 5580 0152 27</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03752</title>
      <link>/stock/K03752/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03752/</guid>
      <description>New and unused ABB electric motor, type M3AA225SMC4, 55kW, 50Hz, 1478 RPM, shaft diameter 60mm, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03753</title>
      <link>/stock/K03753/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03753/</guid>
      <description>New and unused ABB electric motor, type M2CA315SMA 4 IMB35/IM2001, 132kW, 50Hz, 1486 RPM, shaft diameter 80mm, CE marked. Atlas Copco part number 5580 0152 27</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03755</title>
      <link>/stock/K03755/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03755/</guid>
      <description>New and unused ABB electric motor, type M2AA180MLB4, 22kW, 50Hz, 1465 RPM, shaft diameter 48mm, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03757</title>
      <link>/stock/K03757/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03757/</guid>
      <description>New and unused ABB electric motor, type M3AA225SMC4, 55kW, 50Hz, 1477 RPM, shaft diameter 60mm, CE marked</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03759</title>
      <link>/stock/K03759/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03759/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Michelin 27.00R49 XDR A, E4R, 2-star tyre, 4pcs immediately available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03760</title>
      <link>/stock/K03760/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03760/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Michelin 27.00R49 XDR A, E4R, 2-star tyre, 4pcs immediately available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03761</title>
      <link>/stock/K03761/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03761/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Michelin 27.00R49 XDR A, E4R, 2-star tyre, 4pcs immediately available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03762</title>
      <link>/stock/K03762/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03762/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Michelin 27.00R49 XDR A, E4R, 2-star tyre, 4pcs immediately available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03773</title>
      <link>/stock/K03773/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03773/</guid>
      <description>New Metso swing jaw plate to suit Nordberg-Metso C106 crusher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03777</title>
      <link>/stock/K03777/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03777/</guid>
      <description>Cab to suit Terex RT555 rough terrain crane. In good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03790</title>
      <link>/stock/K03790/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03790/</guid>
      <description>Kenco Cab to suit Caterpillar dozer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03793</title>
      <link>/stock/K03793/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03793/</guid>
      <description>Narrow GP bucket with teeth to suit backhoe or mini excavator, bucket width 46 Cm. Quick release hangers. Bucket is in good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03834</title>
      <link>/stock/K03834/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03834/</guid>
      <description>Grouser agricultural tractor drawbar, 3-point hitch connection, c/w top link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03835</title>
      <link>/stock/K03835/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03835/</guid>
      <description>Grouser agricultural tractor drawbar, 3-point hitch connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03836</title>
      <link>/stock/K03836/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03836/</guid>
      <description>Grouser Products type 4500 dozer blade to suit agricultural tractor, complete blade with quick hitch linkage, including hydraulic cylinders, tilt cylinder, blade width 12ft ( 3.60 Mtr.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03837</title>
      <link>/stock/K03837/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03837/</guid>
      <description>Grouser Products agricultural tractor front quick hitch linkage to suit attachments, including hydraulic cylinders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03850</title>
      <link>/stock/K03850/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03850/</guid>
      <description>Volvo L220F Heavy duty rock bucket with teeth, completely refurbished bucket, new bucket tips, new paint. Bucket is immediately available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03855</title>
      <link>/stock/K03855/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03855/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D4H ripper, multi shank ripper with full set of teeth. Complete ripper in very good condition to suit Cat D4H dozer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03869</title>
      <link>/stock/K03869/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03869/</guid>
      <description>Counterweight to suit D7R or similar size dozer, c/w drawbar &amp;amp; storage box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03880</title>
      <link>/stock/K03880/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03880/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Stiebel pump drive unit, Stiebel part number 4596.03.09904.97, Sandvik part number 5196543, max. input power 200kW, max. 1800 RPM, i=0,7846/:0</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03881</title>
      <link>/stock/K03881/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03881/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Stiebel pump drive unit, Stiebel part number 4596.03.09904.97, Sandvik part number 5196543, max. input power 200kW, max. 1800 RPM, i=0,7846/:0</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03884</title>
      <link>/stock/K03884/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03884/</guid>
      <description>Ymer Air/Water/Oil cooler, Metso part number MM0261680. 8 coolers available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03885</title>
      <link>/stock/K03885/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03885/</guid>
      <description>Ymer Air/Water/Oil cooler, Metso part number MM0261680. 8 coolers available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03887</title>
      <link>/stock/K03887/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03887/</guid>
      <description>Unused Good Year tyre 18.00R33, RL-2F, 191B Unisteel E-2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03888</title>
      <link>/stock/K03888/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03888/</guid>
      <description>Brand new Continental 125&amp;frasl;75-8 SC20 SIT solid tyre</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03889</title>
      <link>/stock/K03889/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03889/</guid>
      <description>Brand new Continental 125&amp;frasl;75-8 SC20 SIT solid tyre</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03900</title>
      <link>/stock/K03900/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03900/</guid>
      <description>Parker Stand Up Cement/ Filler Silo, approx 40 M3 (60Ton Capacity), c/w pinch valve, dust filter,platform. Suitable for Cement / Filler / Powder etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03901</title>
      <link>/stock/K03901/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03901/</guid>
      <description>Feed bin c/w belt feeder (set of 2 bins), each bin hold approx 15,000 kgs of stone/sand. Suitable for Asphalt Plant / Concrete Plant or Blending Plant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03902</title>
      <link>/stock/K03902/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03902/</guid>
      <description>Feed bin c/w belt feeder (set of 2 bins), each bin hold approx 15,000kg of stone / sand, suitable for Asphalt Plant / Concrete Plant / Blending Plant</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03907</title>
      <link>/stock/K03907/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03907/</guid>
      <description>Parker 8.78 mtr screw conveyor, diameter 310 mm. c/w Gearbox Drive &amp;amp; Electric Motor. Suitable for Asphalt / Concrete batching plant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03908</title>
      <link>/stock/K03908/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03908/</guid>
      <description>6.53 mtr screw conveyor, diameter 310 mm. suitable for Asphalt/Concrete Batching Plant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03920</title>
      <link>/stock/K03920/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03920/</guid>
      <description>New and unused truck/trailer rims size 22.5x9.00, 10 bolt holes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03932</title>
      <link>/stock/K03932/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03932/</guid>
      <description>Bucket to suit Caterpillar 320BL, bucket width 204 Cm, pin size 80mm, stick 320mm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03935</title>
      <link>/stock/K03935/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03935/</guid>
      <description>New flat chisel for rock breaker, length 1050mm, diameter 115mm, single retaining area, suitable for Rammer S54, Caterpillar H115, JCB HM560</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03937</title>
      <link>/stock/K03937/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03937/</guid>
      <description>Counterweight to suit Cat D6H/D6R/D6T or similar size dozer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03948</title>
      <link>/stock/K03948/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03948/</guid>
      <description>New and unused ABB electric motor, type M2BA 280SA IMB3/IM1001, 75kW, 50Hz, 1485 RPM, CE marked</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03949</title>
      <link>/stock/K03949/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03949/</guid>
      <description>New and unused ABB electric motor, type TEFC M3BP 280SMB 2 IMB3/IM1001 , 90kW, 60Hz, 3573 RPM, CE marked</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03955</title>
      <link>/stock/K03955/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03955/</guid>
      <description>New multi shank ripper to suit Cat 14H motor grader, c/w 5 shanks &amp;amp; hydraulic hoses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03963</title>
      <link>/stock/K03963/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03963/</guid>
      <description>OM Block handling forks to suit Cat 980H/K or similar size wheelloader, quick hitch fittings, fork length 1.24 Mtr, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03970</title>
      <link>/stock/K03970/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03970/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Caterpillar C4.4 engine, arrangement number 454-4421, 4 cylinder turbocharged engine with 142HP (106kW), 4.40 Ltr displacement, factory kit including aftertreatment. 4 Engines available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03985</title>
      <link>/stock/K03985/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03985/</guid>
      <description>O-rops to suit Cat 980C wheel loader, original Caterpillar in good condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03990</title>
      <link>/stock/K03990/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03990/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Caterpillar C4.4 engine, arrangement number 454-4421, 4 cylinder turbocharged engine with 142HP (106kW), 4.40 Ltr displacement, factory kit including aftertreatment. 4 Engines available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03996</title>
      <link>/stock/K03996/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03996/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 3306 engine block, c/w crankshaft, timing gears &amp;amp; flywheel. Removed from Cat 330C excavator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K03999</title>
      <link>/stock/K03999/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K03999/</guid>
      <description>Rockland volume bucket to fit Cat 980G wheel loader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04003</title>
      <link>/stock/K04003/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04003/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Heavy duty Esco cutting edge with tips to fit excavator bucket, width 1.22 Mtr, thickness 50mm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04004</title>
      <link>/stock/K04004/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04004/</guid>
      <description>Unused set Berco CR6333A tracklink assy (2pcs), 36 sect</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04005</title>
      <link>/stock/K04005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04005/</guid>
      <description>Unused set Berco CR6333A tracklink assy (2pcs), 36 sect</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04015</title>
      <link>/stock/K04015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04015/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D11T/R/N ripper shank, length 190Cm, width 38Cm, thickness 85mm, pin holes diameter 95mm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04018</title>
      <link>/stock/K04018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04018/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Cat handled bucket tip pin remover tools, Cat part number 196-1331</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04019</title>
      <link>/stock/K04019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04019/</guid>
      <description>Brand new Yokohama 23.5R25 tyres, Radial RB31 **, E3/L3, fresh production. Large quantity available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04026</title>
      <link>/stock/K04026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04026/</guid>
      <description>Craig front scarifier to suit motor grader, in good and clean condition. Shanks available on request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04030</title>
      <link>/stock/K04030/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04030/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar gear pump 5R-4477, c/w suction tube 5R-4450, suitable for Cat 834B Wheel tractor / 836 Landfill compactor. As-new condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04033</title>
      <link>/stock/K04033/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04033/</guid>
      <description>Kverneland Rau Titan V12 disc harrow, 12 discs, wheel tractor 200-300HP required, crawler tractor 170-220HP required, 15.0/70-18 tyres 80% remaining, new hydraulic hoses, hydraulic cylinders resealed. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04047</title>
      <link>/stock/K04047/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04047/</guid>
      <description>Cummins QSX15 engine / Sullair 20&amp;frasl;12 Drill air compressor kit, 6 cylinder turbocharged, 535 HP @ 2100RPM, CPL 3087, 2x double Rexroth A10V variable displacement axial piston pumps, Sullair 20&amp;frasl;12 High pressure two stage rotary screw drill air compressor kit, 1000 to 1350 CFM (28.3 to 38.2 M3/Min) / (472 to 637 Ltr/Sec) free air delivery, 24 Bar (350PSI). Inspections are welcome!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04048</title>
      <link>/stock/K04048/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04048/</guid>
      <description>Unused Hydac cooler assembly, part number 2302784</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04049</title>
      <link>/stock/K04049/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04049/</guid>
      <description>Unused Hydac cooler assembly, part number 2302784</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04060</title>
      <link>/stock/K04060/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04060/</guid>
      <description>Good used Brake &amp;amp; Planetary gp to suit Cat D8N/D8R dozer. Cat part number 6Y-3588</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04061</title>
      <link>/stock/K04061/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04061/</guid>
      <description>Good used Brake &amp;amp; Differential drive gp to suit Cat D8N/D8R dozer. Cat part number 6Y-3587</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04095</title>
      <link>/stock/K04095/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04095/</guid>
      <description>New manufactured Finlay 14x5 double deck screenbox. Screensize 14ft x 5ft (4.25mtr x 1.5mtr). c/w 15kW electric motor, meshes fitted on top and bottom screen deck., screen is mounted on a modular subframe structure. Walkways fitted on both sides. Can screen up to 400tph. Chutes, Conveyors, etc. can be supplied at extra cost on request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04097</title>
      <link>/stock/K04097/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04097/</guid>
      <description>Bucket with teeth to suit 20-30 Ton excavator, 1.45 m3 capacity, including new Verachtert CW-40 hangers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04106</title>
      <link>/stock/K04106/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04106/</guid>
      <description>8 Pieces New tyres size 7.00-16LT</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04151</title>
      <link>/stock/K04151/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04151/</guid>
      <description>Drawbar to fit Cat D7F/D7G dozer, genuine Caterpillar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04189</title>
      <link>/stock/K04189/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04189/</guid>
      <description>Unused trackshoes to fit Cat 345CL, width 30&amp;rdquo; (750mm), single grouser, full set 104pcs. 4 sets available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04190</title>
      <link>/stock/K04190/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04190/</guid>
      <description>Unused trackshoes to fit Cat 345CL, width 30&amp;rdquo; (750mm), single grouser, full set 104pcs. 4 sets available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04191</title>
      <link>/stock/K04191/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04191/</guid>
      <description>Unused trackshoes to fit Cat 345CL, width 30&amp;rdquo; (750mm), single grouser, full set 104pcs. 4 sets available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04192</title>
      <link>/stock/K04192/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04192/</guid>
      <description>Unused trackshoes to fit Cat 345CL, width 30&amp;rdquo; (750mm), single grouser, full set 104pcs. 4 sets available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04197</title>
      <link>/stock/K04197/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04197/</guid>
      <description>Cat 3304DI engine Ex Army, only 500 running hours from new! Arrangement number 5R7277. Engine is in As-new condition!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04202</title>
      <link>/stock/K04202/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04202/</guid>
      <description>Drawbar to fit Cat D7F/D7G dozer, genuine Caterpillar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04203</title>
      <link>/stock/K04203/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04203/</guid>
      <description>Cat bucket with teeth &amp;amp; cutting edge to suit Cat 345CL or similar size excavator, bucket width 1.10 Mtr, pin sizes 110mm / 90mm, stick width 490mm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04212</title>
      <link>/stock/K04212/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04212/</guid>
      <description>New &amp;amp; unused Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine, Tier 4 Final emission, EPA approval, 6 cylinder turbocharged, 225HP (168kW), arrangement number 452-9413, c/w exhaust muffler and aftertreatment 470-0244 (Cat Regeneration System). Engine fits in Cat 326F/329F/330F/335F - M318F/M322F - MH3022/MH3024/MH3037 - 930M/950M/962M - D6N (subject to configuration)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04216</title>
      <link>/stock/K04216/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04216/</guid>
      <description>O-ROPS cab to suit Caterpillar 140G/140H motorgrader. Rops is in clean and straight condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04240</title>
      <link>/stock/K04240/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04240/</guid>
      <description>Rebuilt Genuine Komatsu D375A track groups, heavy duty 610mm pads with new grouser bars, track groups c/w master shoes and master links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04241</title>
      <link>/stock/K04241/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04241/</guid>
      <description>New &amp;amp; Unused Genuine Komatsu D155AX Sigma dozer blade, blade capacity 9.4 M3, complete package including push arms, tilt cylinder, linkages, pins. 2 Sets available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04242</title>
      <link>/stock/K04242/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04242/</guid>
      <description>New &amp;amp; Unused Genuine Komatsu D155AX Sigma dozer blade, blade capacity 9.4 M3, complete package including push arms, tilt cylinder, linkages, pins. 2 Sets available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04259</title>
      <link>/stock/K04259/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04259/</guid>
      <description>Geith bucket with teeth, pin size 80mm, stick width 310mm, bucket width 63 Cm, CE marked. Bucket is in good condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04264</title>
      <link>/stock/K04264/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04264/</guid>
      <description>Ditch cleaning bucket to suit 20-25 Ton excavator, width 203Cm, pins 80mm, stick width 310mm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04265</title>
      <link>/stock/K04265/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04265/</guid>
      <description>Boom lift cylinder to suit Fiat-Hitachi FH300 excavator. LH + RH side in stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04266</title>
      <link>/stock/K04266/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04266/</guid>
      <description>Boom lift cylinder to suit Fiat-Hitachi FH300 excavator. LH + RH side in stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04272</title>
      <link>/stock/K04272/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04272/</guid>
      <description>Hydraulic quick coupler to suit wheel loader or telehandler. Forks to suit in stock. Part is in good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04274</title>
      <link>/stock/K04274/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04274/</guid>
      <description>Ditch cleaning bucket to suit 20-25 Ton excavator, cutting edge, pins 80mm, stick width 310mm. Bucket is in good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04288</title>
      <link>/stock/K04288/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04288/</guid>
      <description>Ditch cleaning bucket with bolt on cutting edge, pin size 80mm, stick width 310mm, bucket width 2.10 Mtr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04289</title>
      <link>/stock/K04289/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04289/</guid>
      <description>Low hours Volvo L70D transmission, including 2 hydraulic pumps. Transmission is in very good and clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04299</title>
      <link>/stock/K04299/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04299/</guid>
      <description>New GP bucket with teeth to suit 12-15 Ton excavator, bucket width 1.25 Mtr (48&amp;rdquo;), pin diameter 65mm, stick width 260mm, pin centers 420mm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04311</title>
      <link>/stock/K04311/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04311/</guid>
      <description>Track adjuster gp / idler to fit Cat 330D excavator, Cat part number 239-4321, Berco CR6118</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04312</title>
      <link>/stock/K04312/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04312/</guid>
      <description>Track adjuster gp / idler to fit Cat 330D excavator, Cat part number 239-4321, Berco CR6118</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04313</title>
      <link>/stock/K04313/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04313/</guid>
      <description>Final drive gp / track motor to fit Cat 330D excavator. Cat part number 227-6188 / 271-6376</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04314</title>
      <link>/stock/K04314/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04314/</guid>
      <description>Final drive gp / track motor to fit Cat 330D excavator. Cat part number 227-6188 / 271-6376</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04315</title>
      <link>/stock/K04315/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04315/</guid>
      <description>Mono moom gp 6.18 Mtr (20.3 FT) to fit Cat 330D excavator. Cat part number 290-9248. Can be painted Cat yellow on request at extra costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04316</title>
      <link>/stock/K04316/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04316/</guid>
      <description>Stick GP-Hoe 2.55Mtr (8.4 FT) to fit Cat 330D excavator, TB1-Family. Cat part number 290-9287. Excluding bucket cylinder, including bucket linkage. Can be painted Cat yellow on request at extra costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04322</title>
      <link>/stock/K04322/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04322/</guid>
      <description>Drive gp-swing to fit Cat 330D excavator. Cat part number 199-4538</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04347</title>
      <link>/stock/K04347/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04347/</guid>
      <description>Unused Cab to fit Cat 120H/140H/160H or similar size motorgrader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04355</title>
      <link>/stock/K04355/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04355/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 815B padfoot compactor wheel gp, full set 4pcs. Cat part number 2V-7825 / 4V8646 / 4V-8644</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04357</title>
      <link>/stock/K04357/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04357/</guid>
      <description>New heavy duty bucket with teeth and side cutters to fit Cat 345B/350B or similar size excavator, bucket width 1.47 Mtr (58&amp;rdquo;), pin diameter 100-80mm, stick width 440mm, pin centers 550mm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04359</title>
      <link>/stock/K04359/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04359/</guid>
      <description>New heavy duty bucket with teeth and side cutters to fit Cat 320 / Volvo EC210 / Hyundai R210 or similar size excavator, bucket width 1.14 Mtr, pin diameter 80mm, stick width 325mm, pin centers 460mm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04361</title>
      <link>/stock/K04361/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04361/</guid>
      <description>GP bucket to suit 12-15 Ton excavator, bucket width 1.20 Mtr, pin diameter 65mm, stick width 260mm, pin centers 390mm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04362</title>
      <link>/stock/K04362/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04362/</guid>
      <description>Iveco 4 cilinder turbocharged engine, 90HP, very very powerful, from sprayingtractor Video available of oilpressuretest Type 8141.27</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04363</title>
      <link>/stock/K04363/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04363/</guid>
      <description>Iveco 3 cylinder engine, 60HP, (from sprayingtractor), working order Type 8031 I</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04370</title>
      <link>/stock/K04370/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04370/</guid>
      <description>New &amp;amp; unused Strickland GP excavator bucket to fit 20-25 Ton excavator, pins 80mm, stick width 310mm, pin centers 450mm. Several units available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04394</title>
      <link>/stock/K04394/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04394/</guid>
      <description>Counterweight + drawbar to fit Caterpillar D8T/D8R dozer, genuine Caterpillar. Cat part number 217-3654</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04398</title>
      <link>/stock/K04398/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04398/</guid>
      <description>Used Sandvik (Svedala) heavy duty vibrating grizzly feeder, 4.2m x 1.1m (14ft x 42&amp;rdquo;), c/w 2 section step grizzly, invicta electic motors (2), springs. Unit can be supplied with subframe / hopper etc at extra cost if required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04400</title>
      <link>/stock/K04400/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04400/</guid>
      <description>GP bucket with cutting edge, bucket width 1.06 Mtr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04401</title>
      <link>/stock/K04401/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04401/</guid>
      <description>Transmission to fit Cat 416 backhoe loader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04402</title>
      <link>/stock/K04402/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04402/</guid>
      <description>Perkins 4.236 engine, 4 cylinder, 62HP. Engine does not run, for parts or repair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04403</title>
      <link>/stock/K04403/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04403/</guid>
      <description>6 cylinder diesel engine</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04405</title>
      <link>/stock/K04405/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04405/</guid>
      <description>Hydraulic tilt bucket with cutting edge, bucket width 2.20 Mtr, Verachtert CW40 quick coupler connection, incl. hydraulic hoses / quick release fittings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04435</title>
      <link>/stock/K04435/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04435/</guid>
      <description>Blade to fit Cat D6H/D6R/D6T dozer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04436</title>
      <link>/stock/K04436/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04436/</guid>
      <description>2016 Laurini 48&amp;rdquo;-60&amp;rdquo; 50 Ton pipeline Roll Cradle for smooth inline travel operations. 4 mooring points, the rollers distribute the pressure on the pipe to avoid damage to the pipe and coating. Available for sale or rent. For more info please email: john@deltaheavymachinery.com or call +31 653853392.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04437</title>
      <link>/stock/K04437/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04437/</guid>
      <description>2016 Laurini 48&amp;rdquo;-60&amp;rdquo; 50 Ton pipeline Roll Cradle for smooth inline travel operations. 4 mooring points, the rollers distribute the pressure on the pipe to avoid damage to the pipe and coating. Available for sale or rent. For more info please email: john@deltaheavymachinery.com or call +31 653853392.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04438</title>
      <link>/stock/K04438/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04438/</guid>
      <description>2016 Laurini 48&amp;rdquo;-60&amp;rdquo; 50 Ton pipeline Roll Cradle for smooth inline travel operations. 4 mooring points, the rollers distribute the pressure on the pipe to avoid damage to the pipe and coating. Available for sale or rent. For more info please email: john@deltaheavymachinery.com or call +31 653853392.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04443</title>
      <link>/stock/K04443/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04443/</guid>
      <description>XROK 205S-2 static 2 deck scalping/finishing screen. Screen size 20ft x 5ft (6m x 1.5m). c/w 15kW electric motor (not shown on pictures). Meshes fitted on top and bottom screen deck. Screen is mounted on a heavy duty frame. Can screen up to 600tph in scalping configuration, up to 400tph in final screening configuration. Chutes, Sub frames, Conveyors, etc. can be supplied at extra cost on request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04482</title>
      <link>/stock/K04482/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04482/</guid>
      <description>Drawbar to suit Cat D6H/D6R/D6T dozer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04483</title>
      <link>/stock/K04483/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04483/</guid>
      <description>Counterweight to fit Cat D9T dozer, genuine Caterpillar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04525</title>
      <link>/stock/K04525/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04525/</guid>
      <description>Ditch cleaning bucket with cutting edge to suit Cat 336&amp;frasl;340 or similar size excavator, fits Cat TB linkage, bucket width 2.50 Mtr, pin diameter 100-80mm, stick width 441mm, pin centers 587mm, CE marked. Bucket is in as-new condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04526</title>
      <link>/stock/K04526/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04526/</guid>
      <description>Ditch cleaning bucket with cutting edge to suit Cat 336&amp;frasl;340 or similar size excavator, fits Cat DB linkage, bucket width 2.50 Mtr, pin diameter 100-90mm, stick width 385mm, pin centers 500mm, CE marked. Bucket is in as-new condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04527</title>
      <link>/stock/K04527/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04527/</guid>
      <description>Ditch cleaning bucket with cutting edge to suit Cat 336&amp;frasl;340 or similar size excavator, fits Cat DB linkage, bucket width 2.50 Mtr, pin diameter 100-90mm, stick width 385mm, pin centers 500mm, CE marked. Bucket is in as-new condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04542</title>
      <link>/stock/K04542/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04542/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar bucket with teeth to fit Cat 320E or similar size excavator, bucket width 1.42 Mtr, pin diameter 80mm, stick width 315mm, pin centers 445mm. Cat part number 468-4327</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04543</title>
      <link>/stock/K04543/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04543/</guid>
      <description>New Metso fixed jaw plate to suit Nordberg-Metso C105 crusher. Part number 928918</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04544</title>
      <link>/stock/K04544/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04544/</guid>
      <description>New Metso fixed jaw plate to suit Nordberg-Metso C105 crusher. Part number 928918</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04547</title>
      <link>/stock/K04547/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04547/</guid>
      <description>Blade GP-Semi Universal to fit Cat D9R/D9T dozer, removed from 2015 machine with only 3000Hrs, good cutting edge. Cat part number 380-0618</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04548</title>
      <link>/stock/K04548/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04548/</guid>
      <description>Unused boom set to fit Cat 345DL/349DL excavator, boom AR-MASS length 6.60 Mtr (21.6 FT), stick AR-HOE length 2.50 Mtr (8.2 FT), including hydraulic cylinders. Cat part number boom 235-7721, Cat part number stick 228-5447. Complete set including hydraulic pipes, hydraulic hoses and bucket linkage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04549</title>
      <link>/stock/K04549/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04549/</guid>
      <description>Unused boom lift cylinder to fit Cat 345DL/349DL, Cat part number 225-4523. 2 Pieces available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04551</title>
      <link>/stock/K04551/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04551/</guid>
      <description>Unused bucket cylinder to fit Cat 345DL/349DL, Cat part number 225-4532</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04572</title>
      <link>/stock/K04572/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04572/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Geith hydraulic quick coupler to suit 40-50 Ton excavator, front &amp;amp; rear safety lock, pin diameter 100mm, stick width 480mm, pin centers 625mm, CE marked. Multiple units immediately available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04574</title>
      <link>/stock/K04574/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04574/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Geith hydraulic quick coupler to suit 40-50 Ton excavator, front &amp;amp; rear safety lock, pin diameter 110mm, stick width 440mm, pin centers 540mm, CE marked. Multiple units immediately available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04580</title>
      <link>/stock/K04580/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04580/</guid>
      <description>New and unused heavy duty Geith digging bucket with teeth to suit 35-45 Ton excavator, bucket with 1.70 Mtr (66&amp;rdquo;), bucket capacity 2.17 M3, pin diameter 100mm, stick width 410mm, pin centers 555mm, lifting eye SWL 35.000 Kg, CE marked. Bucket is immediately available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04595</title>
      <link>/stock/K04595/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04595/</guid>
      <description>OM Excavator ripper to suit 30-40 Ton excavator, pin diameters 100mm/110mm, pin centers 570mm, stick width 440mm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04599</title>
      <link>/stock/K04599/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04599/</guid>
      <description>Unused stick cylinder to fit Cat 345DL/349DL, Cat part number 225-4526</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04610</title>
      <link>/stock/K04610/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04610/</guid>
      <description>E-ROPS Cab to suit Caterpillar D9H or similar size dozer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04612</title>
      <link>/stock/K04612/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04612/</guid>
      <description>Lameter 40 Ton block handling forks to suit Cat 988G/H or similar size wheel loader, fits Caterpillar quick coupler model 190-0948</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04615</title>
      <link>/stock/K04615/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04615/</guid>
      <description>Verachtert SW2007 hydraulic quick coupler to fit Cat 950K/950M/962K/962M or similar size wheel loader, model 368-9119</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04626</title>
      <link>/stock/K04626/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04626/</guid>
      <description>Verachtert CW-30 hydraulic quick coupler, pin diameter 70mm, stick width 280mm, pin centers 460mm. Bucket to suit available at extra costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04628</title>
      <link>/stock/K04628/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04628/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Fuerst M200G ground drive manure spreader, dimensions 70x170 Cm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04629</title>
      <link>/stock/K04629/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04629/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Farm Wagon 20 trailer, dimensions 90x150 Cm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04630</title>
      <link>/stock/K04630/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04630/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Farm Cart 12 trailer, dimensions 80x120 Cm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04631</title>
      <link>/stock/K04631/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04631/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Farm Cart 20 trailer, dimensions 90x150 Cm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04632</title>
      <link>/stock/K04632/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04632/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Farm Cart 20 trailer, dimensions 90x150 Cm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04633</title>
      <link>/stock/K04633/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04633/</guid>
      <description>Unused Peecon blade, width 2.00 Mtr, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04634</title>
      <link>/stock/K04634/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04634/</guid>
      <description>Unused Peecon blade, width 2.50 Mtr, CE marked. Multiple units available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04639</title>
      <link>/stock/K04639/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04639/</guid>
      <description>Set used triple grouser trackshoes 700mm (27.6 Inch) to fit Cat 330D/336D/336E/336F, 98 pieces. Cat part number 238-8591</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04640</title>
      <link>/stock/K04640/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04640/</guid>
      <description>Set used triple grouser trackshoes 700mm (27.6 Inch) to fit Cat 330D/336D/336E/336F, 98 pieces. Cat part number 238-8591</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04642</title>
      <link>/stock/K04642/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04642/</guid>
      <description>4 Pieces Good Year 23.5R25, 2 Star, E4/L4, GP-4D Unisteel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04645</title>
      <link>/stock/K04645/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04645/</guid>
      <description>Set rear fenders for Cat 950K / 962K wheel loader. Cat part numbers 367-2582 / 367-2583. Fender AS LH 339-9107 / Fender AS RH 339-8841. Complete set including hinge groups in good condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04655</title>
      <link>/stock/K04655/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04655/</guid>
      <description>Set trackgroups (2pcs) to fit Caterpillar D6R/D6R2/D6T dozer, SALT, Extreme service, 38 sect, 560mm (22&amp;rdquo;) single grouser shoes, genuine Caterpillar. Cat part number 385-5458 (Tracklink assy 424-0842). Used idlers and sprockets available on request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04656</title>
      <link>/stock/K04656/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04656/</guid>
      <description>Set used triple grouser trackshoes 900mm (35.4 Inch) to fit Cat 345D/349D/349E/352F, 104 pieces, genuine Cat. Cat part number 150-4767</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04658</title>
      <link>/stock/K04658/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04658/</guid>
      <description>Drawbar to fit Cat D8K/D8H dozer, genuine Caterpillar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04680</title>
      <link>/stock/K04680/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04680/</guid>
      <description>Deutz F2L612 engine. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>V00008</title>
      <link>/stock/V00008/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/V00008/</guid>
      <description>Deutz 8.31 Agrostar, cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged air cooled Deutz BF6L513R engine with 230HP (169kW), 9.572 ltr. displacement, 4WD, full powershift 18&amp;frasl;9 transmission, 40Km/h, 3 point linkage, PTO 1000RPM, 3 hydr. spoolvalves, air brakes, drawbar, front and rear work lights, full set front weights, air suspended seat, 580/70R42 and 520/70R30 tyres. Very strong tractor, in very clean condition. Very rare model, only 47 units built! Tractor is included German registration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>V00015</title>
      <link>/stock/V00015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/V00015/</guid>
      <description>Deutz D4006A, Deutz F3L912 3 cylinder engine, 40 HP, 4-WD Sige 3500 axle, 3 point linkage, 540&amp;frasl;1000 PTO. Tractor is in good and clean condition, tyres 13.6-28 and 7.50-18. Wir sprechen Deutsch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>V00022</title>
      <link>/stock/V00022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/V00022/</guid>
      <description>Ford 2600 farmtractor in mint condition, 3 cylinder engine 34 HP, canopy, original power steering, 1 spoolvalve, 3-pointlinkage and pto, original condition!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>V00060</title>
      <link>/stock/V00060/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/V00060/</guid>
      <description>Lanz Bulldog D9506, 45PS halbraupe, gutes laufwerk, baujahr 1951, 6 gang getriebe, guter original zustand, schone patina, lauft gut, kuhler sind schon, 7.50-20 forder rader. Schlepper kann jeder zeit besichtigt werden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>V00070</title>
      <link>/stock/V00070/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/V00070/</guid>
      <description>Very rare Ford Mailam 5001L-6 agricultural crawler tractor, 6 cylinder engine, 112HP, (Ford 5000 super six engine and transmission) ex farm condition, original paint, auxiliary hydraulics, drawbar, very good undercarriage, only very few of this type of tractor was produced. Collectors item! Inspection are welcome. Road/Sea transport can be arranged!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>V00074</title>
      <link>/stock/V00074/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/V00074/</guid>
      <description>Tractorpulling tractor with DAF 1160DKX engineblock (ex Dakar), big injectionpump, 4 turbochargers, waterinjection, Firestone 30.5-32 tractorpulling tyres</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>V00084</title>
      <link>/stock/V00084/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/V00084/</guid>
      <description>Deutz D5006, 4WD Sige 3500 axle, Deutz F3L912 3 cylinder engine with 50HP, 540&amp;frasl;1000 life PTO. 8 + 4 transmission, powersteering, 14.9-28 and 10.5-18 tyres. Tractor is in good and clean condition. German KFZ brief available. Wir sprechen Deutsch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>V00088</title>
      <link>/stock/V00088/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/V00088/</guid>
      <description>Deutz D6005, Deutz F4L812D engine, 56HP, 9&amp;frasl;3 gearbox, 7.50-16 and 16.9-30, trailerhitch, 540&amp;frasl;1000 PTO, ex farm site and good condition, engine needs overhaul, as-is sale only</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Y00166</title>
      <link>/stock/Y00166/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/Y00166/</guid>
      <description>Brand new Barrier Mould. Quick release design to separate concrete product from steel mould. Key management of waste and left over readymix concrete complies with environmental waste management. Mobile designed concrete barrier mould which can be used as a temporary or stationery barrier structure. Interlock system to join each barrier mould. Forklift facility to locate moulds in position on site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Y00167</title>
      <link>/stock/Y00167/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/Y00167/</guid>
      <description>Brand new 50 Tonne Low Level Storage Silos. High quality robust heavy duty steel design for long life and portability. All safety features to BS standards. Very low ground pressure to provide cost savings in relation to expensive foundations. Maintenance procedures are easily carried out due to silo design. Air compressor mounted on support frame of silo. Electric and pneumatic control panels mounted on silo (option generator supplied). V Trough screw to empty silo and transfer screw conveyor to feed production unit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Y00168</title>
      <link>/stock/Y00168/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/Y00168/</guid>
      <description>Brand new Delta Super block mould. Mould specifications 0.7 m3 &amp;amp; 0.35 m3. Quick release design to spilt mould box. Key management of waste and leftover readymix concrete complies with environmental waste management. Mobile designed concrete block mould which can be used as a temporary or stationery wall structure. Interlock lego type design block moulds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>{{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}   {{ partial &#34;top.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;stock_search_homepage.html&#34; . }}  Delta Machinery   Telephone:	+31 (0) 888 966 966
Fax: +31 (0) 888 966 950
Chambre of commerce number:	17078066
Email: sales@deltamachinery.nl    	Delta Machinery
Mark S. Clarkelaan 6
4761 RK Zevenbergen
The Netherlands
    	Delta Machinery Workshop
Voltstraat 19
5753 RL Deurne
The Netherlands</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>{{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}   {{ partial &#34;top.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;stock_search_homepage.html&#34; . }}  Disclaimer   Delta Machinery (DELTA) disclaims all responsibility and liability for the content on this website. No rights can be derived from the content of this website. DELTA is not liable for direct or indirect loss of whatever kind and whatever basis, due to the use of information that is, or was available on the website of DELTA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gallery/</guid>
      <description>{{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}   {{ partial &#34;top.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;stock_search_homepage.html&#34; . }}  {{ with .Resources.Match &#34;img/*&#34; }} {{ range . }} {{ $image_tn := .Resize &#34;213x142&#34; }} {{ $image_lg := .Resize &#34;1920x&#34; }}  {{ end }} {{ end }}    {{ partial &#34;footer.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;scripts.html&#34; . }}   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/general-terms-and-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/general-terms-and-conditions/</guid>
      <description>{{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}   {{ partial &#34;top.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;stock_search_homepage.html&#34; . }}  General tems and conditions   The general terms and conditions of delivery and sales of Delta Machinery apply.  Download the General Terms and Conditions of delivery and sales of Delta Machinery.       {{ partial &#34;footer.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;scripts.html&#34; . }}   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/history/</guid>
      <description>{{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}   {{ partial &#34;top.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;stock_search_homepage.html&#34; . }}  History   The company was founded in 1987 exporting agricultural tractors. After many years of supplying the agricultural industry, earth moving machinery was added to the inventory and from there onwards became the main focus.  Today, the Delta Group is a full-service supplier that takes care of transportation to any destination in the world, strip down for container loading, shipping, manuals, spare parts and consumables packages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/logistics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/logistics/</guid>
      <description>{{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}   {{ partial &#34;top.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;stock_search_homepage.html&#34; . }}  Delta Logistics   ....  ....     {{ with .Resources.GetMatch &#34;img/logistics_2.jpg&#34;}} {{ $image_tn := .Resize &#34;300x&#34; }} {{end}}  ....    {{ with .Resources.GetMatch &#34;img/logistics_3.jpg&#34;}} {{ $image_tn := .Resize &#34;300x&#34; }} {{end}}  ....     {{ partial &#34;footer.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;scripts.html&#34; .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/machinery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/machinery/</guid>
      <description>{{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}   {{ partial &#34;top.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;stock_search_homepage.html&#34; . }}  Delta Machinery   With a fresh stock of over 300 units sourced from our worldwide network and our own fully equipped workshop with skilled personnel to carry out anything from full refurbishments to single repairs, Delta Machinery is here to assist you with all your heavy equipment needs.  In case the machinery you need is not in stock, we can source, service, inspect and test the equipment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/parts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parts/</guid>
      <description>{{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}   {{ partial &#34;top.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;stock_search_homepage.html&#34; . }}  Delta Parts   The supply of spare parts, wear parts and consumables is an essential part of our customer support, and is handled by the Delta Parts business unit from the Deurne headquarters. We can recommend maintenance packages to keep your heavy machinery running. Parts supply includes engine, transmission and undercarriage parts, wear parts and crusher wear parts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/pipeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pipeline/</guid>
      <description>{{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}   {{ partial &#34;top.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;stock_search_homepage.html&#34; . }}  Delta Pipeline Machinery   Delta Pipeline Machinery is a leading pipeline equipment solutions and services provider with current operations on 4 continents of the world. We have enormous depth of experience, capabilities, skills and resources to provide our clients with the best equipment and service solutions.  Our history and pioneering spirit continues to lay a strong foundation for our future as one of the industry&#39;s leading providers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy/</guid>
      <description>{{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}   {{ partial &#34;top.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;stock_search_homepage.html&#34; . }}  Privacy         Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (&#34;Google&#34;). Google Analytics uses &#34;cookies&#34;, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/rental/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rental/</guid>
      <description>{{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}   {{ partial &#34;top.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;stock_search_homepage.html&#34; . }}  Delta Rental   Delta Rental was created to offer large quantities of quality equipment for specific projects. We rent out equipment on both long- and short term rental periods to minimize the overall capital outlay on your project.  Also, we provide our partners the possibility for Dry rental or we can offer them Tailored Services, depending on the project and wishes of our partners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/</guid>
      <description>{{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}   {{ partial &#34;top.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;stock_search_homepage.html&#34; . }}  Delta Services   We oversee the logistics from the headquarters in Deurne in the Netherlands, which is conveniently located for international shipping.      {{ with .Resources.GetMatch &#34;img/services_2.jpg&#34;}} {{ $image_tn := .Resize &#34;300x&#34; }} {{end}}  Services include taking care of customs and export documentation and insurance as well as organizing the road transport, delivery to port, handling, loading and shipping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshop/</guid>
      <description>{{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}   {{ partial &#34;top.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;stock_search_homepage.html&#34; . }}  Delta Workshop   Our fully equipped (9500 m2) workshop and sandblasting/ painting facility is located in Deurne (the Netherlands), which is well situated for both Rotterdam and Antwerp Ports. Refurbishment, inspection, testing, rebuilding and painting is carried out at our workshop in Deurne. We have a team of professional engineers and mechanics with in-house facilities for repair and maintenance as well as full refurbishment, meaning we are not reliant on outside services or suppliers to meet deadlines.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>