<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Construction on </title>
    <link>/category/construction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Construction on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/category/construction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>E02138</title>
      <link>/stock/E02138/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02138/</guid>
      <description>Terex-Halco 43-22 crawler drill, Cummins 8.3ltr engine, Onboard compressor, 4mtr drill rods, 6 rods carousel, all pins and bushings on mast are replaced, hoses from drill head to dust collector are replaced, many oil hoses are replaced, all repair pictures are available on request, undercarriage has approx. 90% remaining, 400mm pads. Machine has been workshop tested, repaired, has new paint and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02154</title>
      <link>/stock/E02154/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02154/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar TH360B tractor equipped with welding package, generator, welding machines, oxygen platform, rear view camera and other options available on request. 4 cyl. Caterpillar 3054E engine,100hp, E-rops cab,4x4x4 conf., 4 speed power-shuttle transmission 32km/h max speed, 16.9-24 tyres, joy stick &amp;amp; remote controlled hydr. Hiab 071AW 7.2 tm crane, 7.2 mtr max reach, hydr.powered 10bar 1080l/min aircompressor 240ltr air receiver. Other crane and compressor options available on request, 2 hydr. operated front stabilizers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02604</title>
      <link>/stock/E02604/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02604/</guid>
      <description>Speedstar SS2500/SS40 water drilling rig, mounted on heavy duty oilfield tandem axle trailer with Leveling Jacks, Triple Drum Draw Works, Twin (2) Detroit diesel 471 Deck engines with manual transmission, 18 inch rotary table, 18m hydraulically raised mast, (Mast replaced in 2010), with hook block, swivel, operators control station and console, new 11.00-20 tyres. This drilling rig has new paint, is repaired and is in clean condition. Truck is not included.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02640</title>
      <link>/stock/E02640/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02640/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 953 tractor equipped with welding package, generator, welding machines, oxygen platform, rear view camera and other options available on request. 6 cyl. Caterpillar 3116T engine, 120hp, E-rops cab, 10.5km/h max. speed, joy stick &amp;amp; remote controlled hydr. Hiab 071AW 7.2 tm crane, 7.2 mtr max reach, hydr. powered 10 bar 1080l/min aircompressor 240ltr air receiver. Other crane and compressor options available on request. We have many welding tractors in our rental fleet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02750</title>
      <link>/stock/E02750/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02750/</guid>
      <description>Pipe carrier kit fitted on Caterpillar D8T Dozer. Pipe saddles can be changed to transport various pipe diameters from 36 to 60 inches. Kit can be easily removed and re-installed on Cat D8T/R tractor. E-rops cab with air-conditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C15 ACERT Technology engine with 359HP (268kW), 3 speed power-shift transmission, joystick controls, New Caterpillar undercarriage fitted, 600mm pads, 35.000Kgs operating weight, front &amp;amp; rear work lights. 4 Kits available from stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02937</title>
      <link>/stock/E02937/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02937/</guid>
      <description>2001 Hausherr Viper H Series crawler drill rig, c/w enclosed operator cabin, suitable for Down The Hole drilling up to 150mm diamater hole, 81kw Caterpillar/Perkins engine, 4.6m drill mast lenght, 40kn pull down force, 40kn withdrawal force, can take 76-95mm rods, 8 rod carousel, rig has gone through the workshop with many components repaired/replaced where applicable. All repair pictures are available upon request. We have a range of mobile diesel air compressors available to suit if necessary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03829</title>
      <link>/stock/E03829/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03829/</guid>
      <description>New &amp;amp; Unused Ingersoll Rand ECM350 towed wagon drill, c/w IR DTH rotary head, can drill 85 mm to 127mm holes and capacity up to 150m deep, set up for down the hole (DTH) rotation drilling, 3,900 Nm Torque @ 8 bar 10,000LB pullback, takes 3m rods, rig weight 5,443 Kg, 300mm Track Shoes, manifold for water injection, safety check valves on main cylinders.** Drill rods, hammers, tooling etc. can be supplied to customers specification at extra cost on request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04398</title>
      <link>/stock/E04398/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04398/</guid>
      <description>Brand New Xrok Granite 400 self propelled pipeline padding machine, High capacity 2 Deck Screen-Box,11.5 M2 screening area, up to 400 t/ph capacity, many different screen options available to process dry, wet &amp;amp; sticky material, available with 225 HP Caterpillar C7.1, Tier IIIB &amp;amp; Tier 4 Final, CE Marked, Inclined hopper allowing maximum visibility for excavator operator, side to side conveyor with hydraulic deflector plate, 2 speed hydrostatic drive, remote control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04405</title>
      <link>/stock/E04405/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04405/</guid>
      <description>Ingersoll Rand CM780D Crawler Rock Drill, Cab with airconditioning, Remanufactured 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C12 engine with 425HP (317kW), automatic rod changer, pull back force 45.530 N, 2-stage rotary screw air compressor, dust collector + pres cyclone, central grease system, rear view camera, undercarriage on average 80% remaining, 350mm pads, all pipes and drill head included, operating weight 21.000 Kgs, CE marked. 3.428 engine hours, 9.809 Drill hours. Machine is workshop tested and is in good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04406</title>
      <link>/stock/E04406/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04406/</guid>
      <description>Atlas Copco CM780D Crawler Rock Drill, Cab with airconditioning, Remanufactured 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C13 engine with 445HP (317kW) 0 Hours! Automatic rod changer, pull back force 45.530 N, 2-stage rotary screw air compressor, dust collector + pres cyclone, incl. drill rods, rear view camera, undercarriage on average 75% remaining, 350mm pads, operating weight 22.230 Kgs, CE marked. 6.524 machine hours, 3.424 drill hours. Machine is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04457</title>
      <link>/stock/E04457/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04457/</guid>
      <description>Self propelled Phoenix MKVII chip spreader, 4WD, hydraulic extendable spreader 2.50 - 3.85 Mtr working width, canopy, 6 cylinder Ford Powerstar engine, manual transmission, variable speed drum roller, variable speed feed belts, hydraulic folding rear hoppers, 425/65R22.5 Bridgestone tyres, powersteering. Machine is Ex-Government and comes straight from work. Machine has low hours, new paint and is in clean condition. 2 Similar machines available. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04479</title>
      <link>/stock/E04479/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04479/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 422E Backhoe Loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, Cat 3054C Non-electronic turbocharged engine with 94HP (69kW), 4WD, 4 speed transmission, max. speed 40 Km/Hr, hydrostatic steering system, 4-in-1 bucket with teeth and flip-over forks, hydr. extendable stick, operating weight 7.210 Kgs, 12.5&amp;frasl;80-18 front tyres &amp;amp; 16.9-28 rear tyres, front &amp;amp; rear work lights. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04481</title>
      <link>/stock/E04481/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04481/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar CP533E vibrating single drum padfoot roller, 4 cylinder Cat 3054CT turbocharged engine, 130HP (96kW), canopy, 12.000 Kgs operating weight, drum drive, 2 speed hydrostatic drive, 2.13 Mtr drum width, 2 step vibrating, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, 23.1-26 tyres approx. 80% remaining. Machine has low hours and is in clean condition. Inspections welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04762</title>
      <link>/stock/E04762/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04762/</guid>
      <description>New &amp;amp; Unused Ingersoll Rand Drilling Package, Ingersoll Rand ECM350 towed wagon drill, c/w IR DTH rotary head, can drill 85 mm to 127mm holes and capacity up to 150m deep, set up for down the hole (DTH) rotation drilling, 3,900 Nm Torque @ 8 bar 10,000LB pullback, takes 3.1mtr rods, rig weight 5,443 Kg, 300mm track shoes, manifold for water injection, safety check valves on main cylinders, Unused Doosan/Ingersoll-Rand SHP650 High Capacity Portable Air Compressor, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cummins 6CTA8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04862</title>
      <link>/stock/E04862/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04862/</guid>
      <description>Hamm 311 Single drum vibrating roller, Canopy, 4 cylinder Cummins 4BTAA3.9-99C engine with 100HP (74kW), 2 speed hydrostatic transmission, 2 step vibrating, compaction meter, smooth drum, 23.1-26 tyres 90% remaining, operating weight 11.000 Kgs, front &amp;amp; rear work lights. Machine comes straight out of work, has low hours and is in very clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04964</title>
      <link>/stock/E04964/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04964/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Xrok Rotator 380 Recycling Screen available in a tracked or wheeled configuration. Delta Machinery is an authorized distributor for Xrok. Machine is available for sale or rent. Inspections are welcome. Demonstration available. For more info please call +31 888 966 966 or email us at: sales@deltamachinery.nl You can also visit the XROK website: www.xrok.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02429</title>
      <link>/stock/K02429/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02429/</guid>
      <description>Set used drill rods for Terex-Halco rock drill, 75mm diameter, 3 Mtr length, 7 pieces. Drills are straight and in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K02966</title>
      <link>/stock/K02966/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K02966/</guid>
      <description>New and unused Drill rods (9 pcs) to suit Ingersoll-Rand / Atlas Copco rock drills, length 310 Cm, diameter 76mm, thread 2 3&amp;frasl;8&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04436</title>
      <link>/stock/K04436/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04436/</guid>
      <description>2016 Laurini 48&amp;rdquo;-60&amp;rdquo; 50 Ton pipeline Roll Cradle for smooth inline travel operations. 4 mooring points, the rollers distribute the pressure on the pipe to avoid damage to the pipe and coating. Available for sale or rent. For more info please email: john@deltaheavymachinery.com or call +31 653853392.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04437</title>
      <link>/stock/K04437/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04437/</guid>
      <description>2016 Laurini 48&amp;rdquo;-60&amp;rdquo; 50 Ton pipeline Roll Cradle for smooth inline travel operations. 4 mooring points, the rollers distribute the pressure on the pipe to avoid damage to the pipe and coating. Available for sale or rent. For more info please email: john@deltaheavymachinery.com or call +31 653853392.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K04438</title>
      <link>/stock/K04438/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/K04438/</guid>
      <description>2016 Laurini 48&amp;rdquo;-60&amp;rdquo; 50 Ton pipeline Roll Cradle for smooth inline travel operations. 4 mooring points, the rollers distribute the pressure on the pipe to avoid damage to the pipe and coating. Available for sale or rent. For more info please email: john@deltaheavymachinery.com or call +31 653853392.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>