<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quarry Mining_crusher Jaw on Universal</title>
    <link>/categorylinks/quarry-mining_crusher-jaw/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Quarry Mining_crusher Jaw on Universal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categorylinks/quarry-mining_crusher-jaw/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>E02073</title>
      <link>/stock/E02073/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02073/</guid>
      <description>Remanufactured 2012 Terex BL Kue-Ken 915mm X 610mm (36&amp;rdquo; x 24&amp;rdquo;) wheeled jaw crushing plant. Crusher unit fully reconditioned! Capacity up to 180 tph depending on infeed size and product. Electric Drive &amp;amp; switch gear, heavy duty dump hopper, vibrating grizzly section, electric hydraulic power pack, complete new discharge conveyor, complete with new safety rails, ladder and walkways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02368</title>
      <link>/stock/E02368/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02368/</guid>
      <description>Mobile Kue-Ken 114 jaw crusher, up to 250tph, 42x26 (1100x650) vibrating grizzly feeder, folding discharge conveyor. Caterpillar 3306DI engine, overband magnet, triaxle carrier, 4x hydraulic legs, plant came direct from work and in as is condition. Workshop inspection, repairs, repainting available at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03299</title>
      <link>/stock/E03299/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03299/</guid>
      <description>Baxter 900x300mm (36&amp;rdquo;x12&amp;rdquo;) Single Toggle Granulator Jaw Crusher, Remanufactured 2013, modular mounted, suitable for secondary crushing after primary jaw crusher, up to 100 TPH capacity depending on infeed and outfeed size, c/w modular base frame, under crusher cross discharge conveyor, electric motor, output size 90-40mm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03453</title>
      <link>/stock/E03453/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03453/</guid>
      <description>Refurbished Kue-Ken 106, 1100x305mm (42x12&amp;rdquo;) skid mounted modular jaw crusher. New diaphragm, new cheek plates, new keeper plate, new flow switch, new skid mount, new motor stand, new oils and filters. Crusher is in good condition and immediately available. Crusher can be used in a secondary or tertiary application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04336</title>
      <link>/stock/E04336/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04336/</guid>
      <description>Kue-Ken 95 jaw crusher, 915mm X 610mm (36&amp;rdquo; x 24&amp;rdquo;) jaw opening. Up to 180 TPH crushing capacity. Internal mechanism repaired/replaced, Crusher has new paint, is fully workshop inspected and repaired. Wide range of crusher/screening equipment available from stock!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>