<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Telescopic Handlers on Universal</title>
    <link>https://vankessel-it.github.io/subcategories/telescopic-handlers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Telescopic Handlers on Universal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vankessel-it.github.io/subcategories/telescopic-handlers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>E02154</title>
      <link>https://vankessel-it.github.io/stock/E02154/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vankessel-it.github.io/stock/E02154/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar TH360B tractor equipped with welding package, generator, welding machines, oxygen platform, rear view camera and other options available on request. 4 cyl. Caterpillar 3054E engine,100hp, E-rops cab,4x4x4 conf., 4 speed power-shuttle transmission 32km/h max speed, 16.9-24 tyres, joy stick &amp;amp; remote controlled hydr. Hiab 071AW 7.2 tm crane, 7.2 mtr max reach, hydr.powered 10bar 1080l/min aircompressor 240ltr air receiver. Other crane and compressor options available on request, 2 hydr. operated front stabilizers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04070</title>
      <link>https://vankessel-it.github.io/stock/E04070/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vankessel-it.github.io/stock/E04070/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar TH62, enclosed cab with FOPS, Rebuild Caterpillar 3054 engine with 100HP (75kW), 4 speed powershift transmission, 4x4x4 configuration, 4WD, dual axis joystick control, brand new seat, rated load capacity 3.000 Kgs, max. lift height 7.6 Mtr, 7.700 Kgs operating weight, quick coupler, extra hydr. spoolvalve, brand new 17.5LR24 tyres. Machine has new paint, is workshop tested, fully repaired and is in very good and clean condition. Machine is including pallet fork &amp;amp; GP bucket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04478</title>
      <link>https://vankessel-it.github.io/stock/E04478/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vankessel-it.github.io/stock/E04478/</guid>
      <description>Manitou MRT1432 Rotary Telescopic Handler, E-rops cab, Perkins 1104T engine with 101HP (74.5kW), EPA Certified, 2 speed hydrostatic transmission, 4WD, 4x4x4 configuration, forks, mechanical quick coupler, extra hydr. spoolvalve, 4 hydraulic stabilizers, max. lift capacity 3.200 Kgs, max. lift height 13.82 Mtr, max. reach 11.63 Mtr, brand new 16.0/70-20 tyres, operating weight 12.340 Kgs, drawbar, CE marked. Machine is driving but electric &amp;amp; hydraulic system need repairs. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>