<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earthmoving Equipment on Universal</title>
    <link>/categories/earthmoving-equipment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earthmoving Equipment on Universal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/earthmoving-equipment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>E00266</title>
      <link>/stock/E00266/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E00266/</guid>
      <description>Doosan 130LCV, Cab with airconditioning, mono boom, 3.05 Mtr. stick, hammer lines, quick coupler, undercarriage on average 75% remaining, 700mm triple grouser pads, GP digging bucket, work lights, 14.000 Kgs operating weight. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E00293</title>
      <link>/stock/E00293/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E00293/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 769D, 40 ton rigid off-road dump truck with cab fire damage, 3408E Cat engine which is not damaged, bodylinders, retarder, 18.00-33 tyres which are 70% on average. Dump truck is easy to repair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E00360</title>
      <link>/stock/E00360/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E00360/</guid>
      <description>Komatsu WA600-1L Wheel loader, E-ROPS cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder Komatsu SD170 engine with 415 HP, 40.400Kg operating weight, 5.4M3 bucket, 4 step powershift transmission, 35&amp;frasl;65-33 tyres. Machine is in &amp;ldquo;as is&amp;rdquo; running condition and will be sold for spares or repairs. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E00952</title>
      <link>/stock/E00952/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E00952/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D4H dozer, parts machine. Final drives &amp;amp; transmission available. Please contact us for parts / component price &amp;amp; availability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02296</title>
      <link>/stock/E02296/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02296/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 345CL, Excavator pipelayer,10 units available, tipping point 88 ton, 9.2mtr. A-frame boom, cab with heater and airco. Braden planetary dual brake lifting and deriking winch, 2 speed Rexroth hydr. piston motors, 19mm rope diameter, hydr. boom stop, anti-two block system, hydraulic joystick control, 3 side working range, can be transported in one load. Machine is in as new condition. For sales and rental info please contact: Tel. +31653853392 or E-mail: John@deltamachinery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02311</title>
      <link>/stock/E02311/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02311/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 345CL, Excavator pipelayer,10 units available, tipping point 88 ton, 9.2mtr. A-frame boom, cab with heater and airco. Braden planetary dual brake lifting and deriking winch, 2 speed Rexroth hydr. piston motors, 19mm rope diameter, hydr. boom stop, anti-two block system, hydraulic joystick control, 3 side working range, can be transported in one load. Machine is in as new condition. For sales and rental info please contact: Tel. +31653853392 or E-mail: John@deltamachinery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02562</title>
      <link>/stock/E02562/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02562/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D5B, E-rops Cab, Cat 3306DI engine with 105HP (78kW), semi U-blade with tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, drawbar, cutting edge 70% remaining, undercarriage on average 80% remaining, new carrier rollers, new sprockets, 560mm pads, 11.500 Kgs operating weight. Machine has new paint, is workshop tested and is in very good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02943</title>
      <link>/stock/E02943/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02943/</guid>
      <description>Komatsu GD530A-1, Low profile E-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Komatsu diesel engine, powershift transmission, 12ft (3.65 Mtr) moldboard, new cutting edge, centershift, hydr. tipcontrol, scarifier, rear ripper with full set of new shanks, engine enclosures, 14.00-24 tyres 70%. Machine has new paint and is in very clean condition. Inspections are welcome. All manuals are available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02963</title>
      <link>/stock/E02963/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02963/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 938G, E-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3126 engine with 161HP (120kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, bucket capacity 2.50 M3, 20.5-25 tyres on average 40% remaining, front and rear work lights. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome. GP bucket with cutting edge available at extra costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03169</title>
      <link>/stock/E03169/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03169/</guid>
      <description>Ex army Caterpillar 988B 4x4 forklift, Cabin with ROPS &amp;amp; heater, Caterpillar 3408T diesel powered engine 393 HP. Direct injection 65 degree V8 turbo diesel engine. Variable timing fuel system. Power shift transmission. 24 volt direct electric starting system. Full hydraulic steering system with center point frame articulation. Operating weight w/o tophandler 52 ton. 25 ton lifting capacity. Can Stack 20 to 40 Ft containers two high. Top handler attachment. Tire size 35/65R33.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03222</title>
      <link>/stock/E03222/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03222/</guid>
      <description>EPE PL95H, Hydrostatic pipelayers,10 units available, CE marked, 95 ton lifting capacity, Caterpillar C13 Tier IIIA engine 440HP, Linde hydrostatic transmission,10 km/h max speed, 9.0mtr. A frame boom, 2 Braden planetary dual brake winches, 2 speed Rexroth hydr. motors, 19mm rope, hydr. joystick control.
For more info please contact John at Delta Pipeline Machinery: E-mail: John@deltamachinery.nl Phone: +31 888 966 966</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03482</title>
      <link>/stock/E03482/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03482/</guid>
      <description>New and Unused Caterpillar 330D LN, Cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 268HP (200kW), mono boom, 2.15 Mtr stick, hammer lines, check valves, Cat bucket with teeth, 600mm triple grouser shoes, full set of track guides, work lights, 37.000 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine is immediately available! Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03698</title>
      <link>/stock/E03698/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03698/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7G, E-rops cab, Cat 3306 engine, 3 speed powershift transmission, semi U blade/tilt, 610mm pads, undercarriage 75% remaining, drawbar. Machine comes straight out of work and is in ex job site condition. Rear ripper or rear pulling winch available at extra cost. Machine can be painted at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03991</title>
      <link>/stock/E03991/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03991/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar SS-250B soil stabiliser, enclosed cab, ROPS, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat 3406 engine, 3 speed hydrostatic transmission, speed meters miles and KM, 2WD, front and rear steering, tyres front 28L-26, tyres rear 14.9R24, rotor width 240Cm, rotor diameter 120Cm, tips on average 90% remaining (some replaced), PTO driven rotor. Machine comes straight out of work, has new paint and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04269</title>
      <link>/stock/E04269/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04269/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D4E fitted with Midwestern hydraulic pipelayer kit, Caterpillar 3304 engine with 75HP (56kW), ROPS, hydraulic boom and hook winches, rubber boom protection, operating weight approx. 11.000 Kgs, wire ropes in good condition, undercarriage on average 75% remaining. Machine comes straight from job-site and is in very good and clean condition. Machine for sale or rent, subject to terms and conditions. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04333</title>
      <link>/stock/E04333/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04333/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 930 Ex-Army wheel loader, Cab, 4 cylinder Cat 3304 engine with 100HP (75kW), powershift transmission, 20.5R25 Michelin tyres 75% remaining, GP bucket with teeth, engine enclosures, rear counter weight, drawbar, 9.620 Kgs. operating weight. Machine has new paint, very low hours and is in very good technical and optical condition. This is one of the nicest 930&amp;rsquo;s which is available on the market!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04403</title>
      <link>/stock/E04403/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04403/</guid>
      <description>Massey Ferguson 575, 2-door cab, 3-gearlevels, 3-point linkage, PTO, hydr. spoolvalves, 7.50-18 front tyres, 13.6-28 rear tyres. Tractor is in ex farm- and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04467</title>
      <link>/stock/E04467/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04467/</guid>
      <description>Available for rent 20 units Caterpillar 594H S/N# 96V sideboom / pipelayers. All units are frame up rebuilds or fully repaired with servo controlled wet deck conversions, equipped with Braden - Paccar winches with 2 speed Bosch Rexroth hydr. motors, Kawasaki hydr. main pumps, Pat Kruger LML safe load system, Certified ROPS &amp;amp; FOPS fitted, all work orders and pictures of repairs &amp;amp; hydr. conversion available upon request. Tractor has D353 engine 410HP, 3 speed power-shift transmission and drawbar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04479</title>
      <link>/stock/E04479/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04479/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 422E Backhoe Loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, Cat 3054C Non-electronic turbocharged engine with 94HP (69kW), 4WD, 4 speed transmission, max. speed 40 Km/Hr, hydrostatic steering system, 4-in-1 bucket with teeth and flip-over forks, hydr. extendable stick, operating weight 7.210 Kgs, 12.5&amp;frasl;80-18 front tyres &amp;amp; 16.9-28 rear tyres, front &amp;amp; rear work lights. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04488</title>
      <link>/stock/E04488/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04488/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7G Ex-Army dozer, Machine has 462 Hrs from new! O-rops cab with sweeps, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), semi U blade/tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, undercarriage 95% remaining, 610mm pads, rear pulling winch, engine enclosures, new seat, 22.500 Kgs operating weight. Very clean machine!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04533</title>
      <link>/stock/E04533/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04533/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 990H Wheel Loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, manufactured in 2005, first sold in 2012, V12 Turbocharged Aftercooled Cat C27 ACERT Technology engine with 687HP (512kW), EPA compliant, 3 speed powershift transmission, joystick steering, Rock bucket with teeth, rated payload 16.500 Kgs, operating weight 78.000 Kgs, central grease system, 45/65R38 Michelin tyres on average 85% remaining, work lights. Machine comes straight out of work and is in very clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04537</title>
      <link>/stock/E04537/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04537/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336EL, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C9.3 ATAAC engine with 300HP (224kW), Tier 4 Interim, EPA, mono boom, 3.90 Mtr stick, GP Cat bucket with new teeth, hydr. quick coupler, 75% undercarriage, 850mm triple grouser pads, new sprockets, new top rollers, work lights, rear view camera, operating weight 36.100 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04539</title>
      <link>/stock/E04539/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04539/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336EL, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C9.3 ATAAC engine with 300HP (224kW), Tier 4 Interim, EPA, mono boom, 3.20 Mtr stick, GP bucket with new teeth, bucket width 1.40 Mtr, hammer lines, 80% undercarriage, 850mm triple grouser pads, work lights, rear view camera, operating weight 36.100 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04561</title>
      <link>/stock/E04561/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04561/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D8T Dozer, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C15 ACERT Technology engine with 359HP (268kW), Tier 4 Interim, EPA, 4 barrel SS-ripper with hydr. pin puller, differential steering, wrist control steering, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, rear view camera. Machine comes straight out of work and is in very clean condition. Currently located in Houston Texas, USA. Machine is available for sale or rent, subject to terms and conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04618</title>
      <link>/stock/E04618/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04618/</guid>
      <description>Ex-army Caterpillar 130G, Sold new in 2007, only 201 Hrs from new! Machine is in as-new condition, Low profile E-rops cab, 12ft (3.65Mtr) moldboard, scarifier, engine enclosures, 13.00-24 tyres. Machine is in very clean condition. Machine can be repainted in original Cat colors at extra cost. Rear ripper can be supplied at extra cost. Inspections are welcome. 15 units available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04625</title>
      <link>/stock/E04625/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04625/</guid>
      <description>Ex-army Caterpillar 130G, Delivered new in 2002, only 545 Hrs from new! Machine is in as-new condition, Low profile O-rops cab, 12ft (3.65Mtr) moldboard, scarifier, engine enclosures, 13.00-24 tyres. Machine is in very clean condition. Machine can be repainted in original Cat colors at extra cost. Rear ripper can be supplied at extra cost. Inspections are welcome. 15 units available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04626</title>
      <link>/stock/E04626/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04626/</guid>
      <description>Ex-army Caterpillar 130G, Sold new in 2007, only 423 hrs from new! Used for Demo / Training only, Caterpillar engine 147HP, machine is in as-new condition, Low profile E-rops cab, 12ft (3.65Mtr) moldboard, new cutting edge, scarifier, new MS rear ripper fitted, engine enclosures, 13.00-24 tyres. Machine is in very clean and good condition. Operating and parts manual available with the machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04645</title>
      <link>/stock/E04645/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04645/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 320DL, Cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C6.4 ACERT Technology engine with 138HP (103kW), mono boom, 2.92 Mtr stick, hammer lines, check valves, GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 1.35 Mtr, undercarriage on average 70% remaining, 700mm triple grouser pads, new sprockets, new carrier rollers, 22.900 Kgs operating weight, work lights, rear view camera, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04649</title>
      <link>/stock/E04649/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04649/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 320C, Cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Non-electronic Cat 3066TAA engine with 138HP (103kW), EPA Certified, mono boom, Smartboom, 2.90 Mtr stick, check valves, hammer lines, hydr. quick coupler, GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 1.25 Mtr, rear view camera, undercarriage on average 75% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04652</title>
      <link>/stock/E04652/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04652/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 312BL, cab with airconditioning, 4 cylinder turbocharged 3054 engine with 91HP (68kW), mono boom, hydr. quick coupler, ditch cleaning bucket, undercarriage on average 75% remaining, 700mm triple grouser pads, work lights, 12.800 Kgs operating weight. Machine comes straight out of work and is in very clean condition. Inspections are welcome. Expected October 2018</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04664</title>
      <link>/stock/E04664/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04664/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D6T XL, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C9 ACERT Technology engine with 185HP (138kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, wrist control steering, differential steering, semi-U blade with tilt, new cutting edge, undercarriage average 85% remaining, drawbar, counterweight, front &amp;amp; rear work lights. Ripper or winch can be attached at extra cost. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04692</title>
      <link>/stock/E04692/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04692/</guid>
      <description>Ex-army Caterpillar 130G, Sold new in 2008, only 971 hrs on meter. Machine is in as-new condition, Low profile E-rops cab, 12ft (3.65Mtr) moldboard, scarifier, engine enclosures, 13.00-24 tyres. Machine is in very clean condition. Machine can be repainted in original Cat colors at extra cost. Rear ripper can be supplied at extra cost. Inspections are welcome. 15 units available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04695</title>
      <link>/stock/E04695/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04695/</guid>
      <description>Ex-army Caterpillar 130G, Sold new in 2007, Machine is in as-new condition,183 hrs on meter, Low profile E-rops cab, 12ft (3.65Mtr) moldboard with new cutting edge, scarifier, engine enclosures, 13.00-24 tyres. Machine is in very clean condition. Machine can be repainted in original Cat colors at extra cost. Rear ripper can be supplied at extra cost. Inspections are welcome. 15 units available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04719</title>
      <link>/stock/E04719/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04719/</guid>
      <description>Ex-army Caterpillar 130G, Sold new in 2008, Only 600 Hrs on meter! Machine is in as-new condition, Low profile E-rops cab, 12ft (3.65Mtr) moldboard with new cutting edges, scarifier, engine enclosures, 13.00-24 tyres. Machine is in very clean condition. Machine can be repainted in original Cat colors at extra cost. Rear ripper can be supplied at extra cost. Inspections are welcome. 15 units available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04723</title>
      <link>/stock/E04723/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04723/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 12H motor grader, Low profile E-rops cab, 6 cylinder Caterpillar 3306B Non-electronic engine with 165HP (123kW), 8F-6R powershift transmission, 14ft (4.26 Mtr) moldboard, hydr. tip control, centershift, new cutting edge, 14.200 Kgs operating weight, drawbar, 14.00-24 tyres on average 40% remaining. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome. Rear ripper can be fitted on request at extra costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04736</title>
      <link>/stock/E04736/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04736/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D6G XL Series II, delivered new in 2009, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat 3306DIT Non-electronic engine with 162HP (119kW), 3 speed Non-electronic powershift transmission, Semi U-blade with tilt, new cutting edge, undercarriage on average 75% remaining, engine enclosures, front and rear work lights, drawbar, operating weight 16.880 Kgs. Machine has low hours and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04745</title>
      <link>/stock/E04745/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04745/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7F Ex-Army dozer, only 943 hours since new! O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat engine 200HP, Semi U-blade with tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, undercarriage average 90% remaining, 560mm pads, Hyster rear pulling winch. Machine can be supplied including independent Caterpillar TA inspection, can be equipped with a rear ripper and yellow paint at extra costs. Machine is in good and clean condition. 5 Units expected soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04750</title>
      <link>/stock/E04750/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04750/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 824G, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat 3406C engine with 315HP (235kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, blade with double tilt, Command Control Steering, 29.5R29 Bridgestone front tyres &amp;amp; 29.5R29 Michelin rear tyres, 28.495 Kgs operating weight, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, fast fill fuel system, fire suppression system, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04755</title>
      <link>/stock/E04755/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04755/</guid>
      <description>Ex-army Caterpillar 130G, Sold new in 2008, Only 386 Hrs from new! Machine is in as-new condition, Low profile E-rops cab, 12ft (3.65Mtr) moldboard, scarifier, engine enclosures, 13.00-24 tyres. Machine is in very clean condition. New MS rear ripper fitted and new Cat paint. Inspections are welcome. 15 units available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04757</title>
      <link>/stock/E04757/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04757/</guid>
      <description>Ex-army Caterpillar 130G, Sold new in 2007, Only 112 Hrs from new! Machine is in as-new condition, Low profile E-rops cab, 12ft (3.65Mtr) moldboard, new cutting edge, scarifier, engine enclosures, 13.00-24 tyres. Machine is in very clean condition. Machine can be repainted in original Cat colors at extra cost. Rear ripper can be supplied at extra cost. Inspections are welcome. 15 units available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04758</title>
      <link>/stock/E04758/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04758/</guid>
      <description>Ex-army Caterpillar 130G, Sold new in 2009, Only 317 Hrs from new! Machine is in as-new condition, Low profile E-rops cab, 12ft (3.65Mtr) moldboard, scarifier, engine enclosures, 13.00-24 tyres. Machine is in very clean condition. Machine can be repainted in original Cat colors at extra cost. Rear ripper can be supplied at extra cost. Inspections are welcome. 15 units available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04769</title>
      <link>/stock/E04769/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04769/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7F Ex-Army dozer, sold new in 1998, only 527 hrs worked, O-rops cab, Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), Semi U-blade with tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, undercarriage on average 60% remaining, Hyster rear pulling winch. Machine can be supplied including independent Caterpillar TA inspection on request. Can be equipped with rear ripper and painted in Cat yellow at extra costs. Machine is in good and clean condition, inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04776</title>
      <link>/stock/E04776/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04776/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7F Ex-Army dozer, Only 147Hrs from new! O-rops cab with sweeps, Caterpillar 3306 engine with 200HP (149kW), Semi U-blade with tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, Hyster rear pulling winch, engine enclosures. Machine can be supplied including independent Caterpillar TA inspection and can be equipped with a rear ripper at extra costs. Machine is in good and clean condition, inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04778</title>
      <link>/stock/E04778/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04778/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D8R Dozer, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3406 engine with 320HP (235kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, differential steering, semi U-blade with tilt, 4-barrel single shank ripper with new wear parts, undercarriage average 80% remaining, 610mm shoes, front &amp;amp; rear work lights. Machine comes straight out of work, has new paint and is in clean condition. Independent Caterpillar TA inspection available on request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04779</title>
      <link>/stock/E04779/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04779/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D8R Dozer, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3406 engine with 320HP (235kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, differential steering, semi U-blade with tilt, new cutting edge fitted, 4-barrel single shank ripper with new wear parts, undercarriage average 80% remaining, 610mm shoes, front &amp;amp; rear work lights. Machine comes straight out of work, has new paint and is in clean condition. Independent Caterpillar TA inspection available on request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04781</title>
      <link>/stock/E04781/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04781/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7F Ex-Army dozer, O-rops cab, Caterpillar 3306 engine with 200HP (149kW), Semi U-blade with tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, Hyster rear pulling winch. Machine can be supplied including independent Caterpillar TA inspection and can be equipped with a rear ripper at extra costs. Machine is in good and clean condition, inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04785</title>
      <link>/stock/E04785/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04785/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D6K Series II LGP, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C6.6 ACERT Technology engine with 158HP (118kW), EPA certified, hydrostatic transmission, 6-way PAT blade, drawbar, extra valve for ripper, Grade Control, undercarriage on average 75% remaining, 760mm pads, front and rear work lights. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04787</title>
      <link>/stock/E04787/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04787/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D8T Dozer, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C15 ACERT Technology engine with 359HP (268kW), Tier 4 Interim, EPA, semi U-blade with tilt, new cutting edge fitted, Allied W12E rear pulling winch, ripper valve, differential steering, wrist control steering, front &amp;amp; rear work lights. Fully serviced and is in very clean condition. Inspections are welcome. Machine is available for sale or rent, subject to terms and conditions. Ripper available upon request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04789</title>
      <link>/stock/E04789/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04789/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 330BL Excavator pipelayer, main machine sold new in 2002, converted into pipelayer in 2014, 3 units available, tipping point 65 ton, 7.3mtr. A-frame boom, Caterpillar 3306 engine, triple grouser pads, cab with heater and airconditioning. Braden planetary dual brake lifting and deriking winch, 2 speed Rexroth hydr. piston motors, 19mm rope diameter, hydr. boom stop, anti-two block system, hydraulic joystick control, 3 side working range, can be transported in one load incl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04792</title>
      <link>/stock/E04792/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04792/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7G Ex-Army dozer, Delivered new in 2001, Only 554Hrs from new! O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, semi U blade with tilt, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 510mm pads, rear pulling winch, 22.500 Kgs operating weight. Rear ripper can be installed at extra cost. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome. Machine can be repainted in Cat yellow at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04793</title>
      <link>/stock/E04793/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04793/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7G Ex-Army dozer, Delivered new in 2010, Only 445Hrs from new! O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, semi U blade with tilt, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 610mm pads, rear pulling winch, 22.500 Kgs operating weight. Rear ripper can be installed at extra cost. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome. Machine can be repainted in Cat yellow at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04794</title>
      <link>/stock/E04794/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04794/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7G Ex-Army dozer, Delivered new in 2004, Only 744Hrs from new! O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, semi U blade with tilt, new cutting edge fitted, undercarriage on average 80% remaining, 510mm pads, rear pulling winch, 22.500 Kgs operating weight. Rear ripper can be installed at extra cost. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04795</title>
      <link>/stock/E04795/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04795/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7G Ex-Army dozer, Delivered new in 2007, Only 619Hrs from new! O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, semi U blade with tilt, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 610mm pads, multi shank rear ripper, 22.500 Kgs operating weight. Inspections are welcome. Machine comes straight out of work and is in very clean condition. Machine can be repainted in Cat yellow at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04796</title>
      <link>/stock/E04796/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04796/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7G Ex-Army dozer, Delivered new in 2007, Only 513Hrs from new! O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, semi U blade with tilt, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 510mm pads, rear pulling winch, 22.500 Kgs operating weight. Rear ripper can be installed at extra cost. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome. Machine can be repainted in Cat yellow at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04800</title>
      <link>/stock/E04800/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04800/</guid>
      <description>Komatsu WA350-3T, O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Komatsu SA6D108E-2 engine, 4 speed powershift transmission, bucket with teeth, work lights, engine enclosures, 20.5-25 tyres, lift cylinders are resealed. Repair pictures available on request. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04802</title>
      <link>/stock/E04802/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04802/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D8T Dozer, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C15 ACERT Technology engine with 359HP (268kW), semi U-blade with tilt, new cutting edge, 4 barrel SS-ripper with hydr. pin puller, differential steering, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, fast fill fuel system, brand new Caterpillar trackgroups fitted, 560mm shoes. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome. Full history available on request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04804</title>
      <link>/stock/E04804/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04804/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 320C LU, Cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Non-electronic Cat 3066TAA engine with 138HP (103kW), mono boom, 2.90 Mtr stick, hammer lines, GP bucket with teeth and side cutters, undercarriage on average 80% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04811</title>
      <link>/stock/E04811/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04811/</guid>
      <description>Komatsu WA200-6 Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 4 cylinder turbocharged Komatsu SAA4D107E-1 engine with 128HP (95kW), EPA Certified, 4 speed hydrostatic transmission, hydraulic quick release with bucket and forks, 20.5R25 tyres 80% remaining, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, engine enclosures. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04813</title>
      <link>/stock/E04813/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04813/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 320BL tracked excavator, cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3116 non-electronic engine with 128HP (96kW), mono boom, 2.90 Mtr stick, hammer lines, brand new GP bucket with teeth, undercarriage on average 70% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, work lights. Machine has been partially repainted and is in very clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04815</title>
      <link>/stock/E04815/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04815/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D9T, E-ROPS cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C18 ACERT Technology engine with 410HP (306kW), 3 speed powershift transmission which is overhauled recently, differential steering, wrist control steering, Fast Fill fuel system, Rebuild SS rear ripper with hydr. pin puller, all ripper cylinders resealed and new hoses, engine enclosures, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, undercarriage on average 85% remaining, 610mm single grouser shoes, 59.700Kgs operating weight, CE marked. New blade installed 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04819</title>
      <link>/stock/E04819/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04819/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7F Ex-Army dozer, Only 1697 Hrs from new! O-rops cab with sweeps, Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), Semi U-blade with tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, undercarriage on average 80% remaining, Hyster rear pulling winch. Machine can be supplied including independent Caterpillar TA inspection and can be equipped with a rear ripper at extra costs. Machine is in good and clean condition, inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04830</title>
      <link>/stock/E04830/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04830/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 587R hydraulic operated pipelayers, delivered new in 2011, 8 units immediately available from stock The Netherlands, 91.625 kg lift capacity, 8.5 mtr boom (28ft) Paccar- Braden planetary winches, Free-fall function on hook line control, 2 speed Rexroth hydr. piston motors, 6 cylinder Caterpillar engine, Enclosed cab, 80% undercarriage, 864mm (34&amp;rdquo;) shoes, 3 speed powershift transmission, drawbar. Machines are in clean condition.
For sale and/or rental information please contact: Tel. +31 653 85 3392 or E-mail: John@deltamachinery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04837</title>
      <link>/stock/E04837/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04837/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 323D2L, Made in Japan, E-ROPS cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 158HP (118kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, 2.90 Mtr stick, hammer lines, GP bucket with new teeth (bucket width 1,12mtr), undercarriage on average 85% remaining, 600mm triple grouser shoes, rear &amp;amp; side view camera, work lights, 25.700 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine has low hours, comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04846</title>
      <link>/stock/E04846/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04846/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7F Ex-Army dozer, Only 1422Hrs from new! O-rops cab, Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 189HP (141kW), Semi U-blade with tilt, new cutting edge, 3 speed powershift transmission, undercarriage on average 80% remaining, Hyster rear pulling winch. Machine can be supplied including independent Caterpillar TA inspection and can be equipped with a rear ripper at extra costs. Machine is in good and clean condition, inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04863</title>
      <link>/stock/E04863/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04863/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D9R Dozer, Ex rental machine, Caterpillar 3408C Non-electronic engine with 443HP (330kW), E-Rops cab with airconditioning, Semi U-blade with tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, new 610mm single grouser pads fitted, single shank ripper, front and rear work lights. 2 units available for sale or rent, subject to terms and conditions. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04864</title>
      <link>/stock/E04864/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04864/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D9R Dozer, Ex rental machine, started working in 2015, Caterpillar 3408C Non-electronic engine with 443HP (330kW), E-Rops cab with airconditioning, Semi U-blade with tilt, 3 speed powershift transmission, 685mm single grouser pads, single shank ripper, front and rear work lights. 2 units available for sale or rent, subject to terms and conditions. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04883</title>
      <link>/stock/E04883/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04883/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2 LME, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, hammer lines, Cat bucket with teeth, hydr. quick coupler, undercarriage 80% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, work lights, 39.400 Kgs operating weight, rear view camera, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04887</title>
      <link>/stock/E04887/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04887/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 988H, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C18 engine with 532HP (397kW), 4 speed powershift transmission, joystick steering, ride control, check valve on tilt cylinder, hydraulic quick coupler, GP bucket with teeth, central grease system, engine enclosures, 56.276 Kgs operating weight, CE marked, Michelin XMINED L-5 tyres 35/65R33 20% remaining. 25 Ton heavy duty block handling forks are available at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04888</title>
      <link>/stock/E04888/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04888/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 330D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 208HP (155kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.65 Mtr, Caterpillar GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 60&amp;rdquo; (1.50mtr), CB linkage family, hammer lines, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, 33.000 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04889</title>
      <link>/stock/E04889/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04889/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 330D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 208HP (155kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.65 Mtr, Caterpillar GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 60&amp;rdquo; (1.50mtr), CB linkage family, hammer lines, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, 33.000 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04890</title>
      <link>/stock/E04890/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04890/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 330D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 208HP (155kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.65 Mtr, Caterpillar GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 60&amp;rdquo; (1.50mtr), CB linkage family, hammer lines, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear view camera, work lights, 33.000 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04891</title>
      <link>/stock/E04891/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04891/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 330D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 208HP (155kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.65 Mtr, Caterpillar GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 60&amp;rdquo; (1.50mtr), CB linkage family, hammer lines, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear view camera, work lights, 33.000 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04892</title>
      <link>/stock/E04892/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04892/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 330D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 208HP (155kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.65 Mtr, Caterpillar GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 60&amp;rdquo; (1.50mtr), CB linkage family, hammer lines, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear view camera, work lights, 33.000 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04893</title>
      <link>/stock/E04893/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04893/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 330D2L, Made in Japan, Delivered new in 2017, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 208HP (155kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.65 Mtr, Caterpillar GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 60&amp;rdquo; (1.50mtr), CB linkage family, hammer lines, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, 33.000 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04894</title>
      <link>/stock/E04894/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04894/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 330D2L, Made in Japan, Delivered new in 2017, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 208HP (155kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.65 Mtr, Caterpillar GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 60&amp;rdquo; (1.50mtr), CB linkage family, hammer lines, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, 33.000 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04895</title>
      <link>/stock/E04895/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04895/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, central lubrication system, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04896</title>
      <link>/stock/E04896/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04896/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04897</title>
      <link>/stock/E04897/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04897/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, Delivered new in 2018, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04899</title>
      <link>/stock/E04899/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04899/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, central lubrication system, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04900</title>
      <link>/stock/E04900/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04900/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04901</title>
      <link>/stock/E04901/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04901/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04902</title>
      <link>/stock/E04902/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04902/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04903</title>
      <link>/stock/E04903/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04903/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, front cab guard, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, hammer lines, hydraulic quick coupler, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04904</title>
      <link>/stock/E04904/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04904/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, front cab guard, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, hammer lines, hydraulic quick coupler, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04905</title>
      <link>/stock/E04905/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04905/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, front cab guard, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, hammer lines, hydraulic quick coupler, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04906</title>
      <link>/stock/E04906/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04906/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, front cab guard, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, hammer lines, hydraulic quick coupler, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04907</title>
      <link>/stock/E04907/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04907/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04908</title>
      <link>/stock/E04908/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04908/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04910</title>
      <link>/stock/E04910/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04910/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 336D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C9 ACERT Technology engine with 285HP (213kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 2.55 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 66&amp;rdquo; (1.65mtr), TB linkage family, central lubrication system, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm triple grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 39.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04911</title>
      <link>/stock/E04911/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04911/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, cab guard, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04912</title>
      <link>/stock/E04912/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04912/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04913</title>
      <link>/stock/E04913/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04913/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04914</title>
      <link>/stock/E04914/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04914/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04915</title>
      <link>/stock/E04915/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04915/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, Delivered new in 2018, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04916</title>
      <link>/stock/E04916/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04916/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, front cab guard, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.30 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04917</title>
      <link>/stock/E04917/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04917/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04918</title>
      <link>/stock/E04918/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04918/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04919</title>
      <link>/stock/E04919/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04919/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, front cab guard, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04920</title>
      <link>/stock/E04920/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04920/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 349D2L, Made in Japan, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat C13 ACERT Technology engine with 409HP (305kW), No aftertreatment/DPF/Adblue, mono boom, stick length 3.00 Mtr, Caterpillar Severe-Duty (SD) bucket with teeth, bucket width 72&amp;rdquo; (1.80mtr), UB linkage family, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 600mm double grouser pads, rear and side view camera, work lights, operating weight 52.400 Kgs, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04921</title>
      <link>/stock/E04921/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04921/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 980H Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C15 ACERT Technology engine with 348HP (260kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, V-rock bucket with teeth, ride control, Command Control Steering, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, 29.5R25 tyres, 31.330 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04922</title>
      <link>/stock/E04922/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04922/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 980H Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C15 ACERT Technology engine with 348HP (260kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, V-rock bucket with teeth, ride control, Command Control Steering, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, 29.5R25 tyres, 31.330 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04924</title>
      <link>/stock/E04924/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04924/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 980H Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C15 ACERT Technology engine with 348HP (260kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, V-rock bucket with teeth, ride control, Command Control Steering, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, 29.5R25 tyres, 31.330 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04925</title>
      <link>/stock/E04925/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04925/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 950GC Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 225HP (168kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, Full steer, GP bucket with teeth, bucket capacity 3.30 M3, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, 23.5R25 tyres, 18.100 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04926</title>
      <link>/stock/E04926/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04926/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 950GC Wheel loader, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C7.1 ACERT Technology engine with 225HP (168kW), 4 speed automatic powershift transmission, Full steer, GP bucket with teeth, bucket capacity 3.30 M3, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, 23.5R25 tyres, 18.100 Kgs operating weight, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04929</title>
      <link>/stock/E04929/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04929/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 434F2 Backhoe loader, Made in UK, E-rops cab with airconditioning, 4 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar C4.4 engine with 101HP (75kW), 6 speed Auto-Shift transmission 40 KM/H, 4WD, All Wheel Steer, multipurpose 4-in-1 bucket with teeth, extendable backhoe stick, side shift frame, GP bucket with teeth, extra auxiliary function, 2 hydraulic stabilizers, front &amp;amp; rear work lights, operating weight 9.130 Kgs, 440&amp;frasl;80-28 tyres, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04940</title>
      <link>/stock/E04940/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04940/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D7G Ex-Army dozer, Delivered new in 2004, Only 897Hrs from new! O-rops cab, 6 cylinder turbocharged Caterpillar 3306DI engine with 200HP (149kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, semi U blade with tilt, undercarriage on average 90% remaining, 510mm pads, rear pulling winch, 22.500 Kgs operating weight. Rear ripper can be installed at extra cost. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition. Inspections are welcome. Machine can be repainted in Cat yellow at extra cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04943</title>
      <link>/stock/E04943/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04943/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar D6R XL, E-rops cab with air conditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat 3306DI engine with 185HP (138kW), 3 speed powershift transmission, differential steering, wrist control steering, A blade with double tilt (not shown on picture), new cutting edge, 610mm shoes, front and rear work lights, engine enclosures, drawbar, rear view camera, operating weight 19.000 Kgs, new carrier rollers and sprockets fitted, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work and is in clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04944</title>
      <link>/stock/E04944/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04944/</guid>
      <description>Caterpillar 322CL, FOPS Cab with airconditioning, 6 cylinder turbocharged Cat 3126B ATAAC engine with 165HP (123kW), cab guard, mono boom, Smartboom, check valves, stick length 2.95 Mtr, hammer lines, extra aux. hydr. function, hydr. quick coupler, GP bucket with teeth, bucket width 1.41 Mtr, undercarriage average 70% remaining, 700mm triple grouser pads, 26.903 Kgs operating weight, work lights, CE marked. Machine comes straight out of work, inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>