<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Truck on Universal</title>
    <link>/category/truck/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Truck on Universal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/category/truck/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>E00127</title>
      <link>/stock/E00127/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E00127/</guid>
      <description>Ford F450, Service truck, V8 Powers stroke diesel engine, 5 speed manual transmission, LHD, standard cab, work bed, welder/generator including cables, fuel tank including pump, 2 air hose reels, bolt on crane, storage boxes, 235/85R16 Michelin tyres 70% remaining. Truck is in good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02595</title>
      <link>/stock/E02595/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02595/</guid>
      <description>2014 new build tray body fitted with twist locks fitted on 2008 used chassis, 88,150 kms, Palfinger 32080 crane fitted with 4 extensions c.w. radio remote control, front and rear telescopic jack legs, upright exhaust, 16 speed manual gearbox, new Pirelli 295/80R22.5 tyres fitted, Mounted on 2008 8x4 Hino 700 series (Very Low Kilometers), 420HP, airco, autolube, right hand drive. Truck is workshop tested and repaired. Truck is in very good and clean condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E02596</title>
      <link>/stock/E02596/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E02596/</guid>
      <description>2014 New manufactured cheese wedge bevertail machinery body, jack legs, fitted on 2008 Hino FYPUKA 700 3241 8x4 truck (Ex Goverment), 118,511 kms, upright exhaust, airco, sunvisor, new Pirelli 295/80R22.5 tyres fitted. 16 spd ZF Gearbox, flashing beacons, c.w. New manufactured cheese wedge bevertail machinery body, jack legs, 35,000 Kgs Design Gross Vehicle Weight, Tare Weight 12,800 Kgs, Design Payload 22,200 Kgs (Depending on local regulations), right hand drive. Truck is workshop inspected and repaired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E03335</title>
      <link>/stock/E03335/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E03335/</guid>
      <description>Hino 700FY with crane, 2007 8x4 Hino 700 series, 420HP, 221,464 kms, body with twist locks, HIAB 220C-5 crane fitted with 5 extensions c.w. radio remote control and rear legs, airco, upright exhaust, 16 speed manual gearbox, NEW Pirelli 295/80R22.5 tyres fitted, reverse camera, aluminium tool lockers, right hand drive. Truck is workshop tested and repaired. Truck is in very good and clean condition. Inspections are welcome!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04374</title>
      <link>/stock/E04374/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04374/</guid>
      <description>MAN TGS32.360 with TEKA concrete pump 42 Mtr, 476,740 km, cab with airconditioning, 8x4 configuration, manual gearbox, 295/80R22.5 tyres.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04576</title>
      <link>/stock/E04576/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04576/</guid>
      <description>AMS PowerProbe 9635 Geotechnical core drill, drill has only 1014 working hours, PTO powered, 175ft lb hydraulic hammer, high speed auger, high pressure pump, 10&amp;rsquo; x 15&amp;rdquo; drill rod, direct push sampling, side-to-side and in-and-out slide base, hollow stem capabilities, 2-speed 5000 ft lb auger drive head, 80&amp;rdquo; probe stroke for use of up to 5&amp;rsquo; tooling, 2400 psi-12GPM pump, hydraulic oil cooler, 33000 lb push down force, 47500 lb pull back force, adjustable mast for angled probing &amp;amp; drilling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04680</title>
      <link>/stock/E04680/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04680/</guid>
      <description>Hino 700FY tarspreader, RHD, twin burners, Rincheval 2.40 - 4.10 Mtr extendable spray bar, spray &amp;amp; distance meter + printer, 8x4 configuration, manual gearbox, 295/80R22.5 tyres, rear view camera. Truck comes straight out of work. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E04690</title>
      <link>/stock/E04690/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stock/E04690/</guid>
      <description>Mercedes-Benz 1820 tarspreader, RHD, 2.40 Mtr spray bar, twin burners, hydraulic bitumen pump, 4x2 configuration, manual gearbox, 12R22.5 tyres on average 85% remaining. Truck is Ex Goverment and comes straight out of work. Inspections are welcome.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>